保,O
护,O
区,O
涉,O
及,O
博,B_LOC
白,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
那,B_LOC
林,I_LOC
镇,I_LOC
和,O
国,O
有,O
博,O
白,O
林,O
场,O
，,O
总,O
面,O
积,O
1,O
6,O
0,O
1,O
2,O
公,O
顷,O
。,O
未,O
经,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
人,O
民,O
政,O
府,O
批,O
准,O
，,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
的,O
面,O
积,O
、,O
范,O
围,O
和,O
功,O
能,O
分,O
区,O
不,O
得,O
调,O
整,O
和,O
改,O
变,O
。,O
5,O
%,O
；,O
国,O
有,O
土,O
地,O
（,O
属,O
国,O
有,O
博,O
白,O
林,O
场,O
）,O
7,O
8,O
公,O
顷,O
，,O
占,O
确,O
界,O
面,O
积,O
的,O
0,O
.,O
5,O
%,O
。,O
二,O
、,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
四,O
至,O
界,O
线,O
北,O
起,O
6,O
7,O
6,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
五,O
方,O
顶,O
）,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
、,O
山,O
谷,O
向,O
南,O
过,O
4,O
4,O
1,O
.,O
8,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
2,O
9,O
6,O
.,O
9,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
3,O
6,O
7,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
2,O
3,O
.,O
1,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
大,O
岭,O
头,O
）,O
、,O
3,O
5,O
3,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
2,O
9,O
6,O
.,O
2,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
3,O
9,O
8,O
.,O
8,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
2,O
8,O
.,O
6,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
百,O
花,O
头,O
）,O
、,O
3,O
9,O
6,O
.,O
2,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
2,O
3,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
青,O
菜,O
头,O
）,O
、,O
3,O
5,O
7,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
0,O
7,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
1,O
2,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
6,O
4,O
7,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
马,O
安,O
头,O
）,O
、,O
5,O
6,O
9,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
9,O
4,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
5,O
4,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
4,O
4,O
.,O
4,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
六,O
洋,O
塘,O
顶,O
）,O
、,O
6,O
0,O
4,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
9,O
8,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
2,O
3,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
6,O
0,O
8,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
三,O
胎,O
头,O
）,O
、,O
5,O
3,O
1,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
7,O
6,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
5,O
1,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
9,O
0,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
梨,O
香,O
头,O
）,O
、,O
4,O
7,O
4,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
4,O
3,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
5,O
7,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
天,O
然,O
穴,O
）,O
、,O
3,O
6,O
8,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
7,O
8,O
3,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
8,O
2,O
2,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
8,O
4,O
7,O
.,O
3,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
鸡,O
冠,O
头,O
）,O
、,O
4,O
6,O
2,O
.,O
1,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
6,O
3,O
.,O
8,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
7,O
3,O
8,O
.,O
1,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
8,O
5,O
2,O
.,O
1,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
云,O
飞,O
嶂,O
）,O
、,O
8,O
0,O
9,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
2,O
4,O
3,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
2,O
8,O
.,O
1,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
8,O
2,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
山,O
塘,O
岭,O
）,O
、,O
2,O
1,O
1,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
4,O
4,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
4,O
2,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
2,O
1,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
过,O
滕,O
塘,O
）,O
、,O
1,O
1,O
8,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
1,O
6,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
4,O
2,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
2,O
1,O
9,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
天,O
堂,O
岭,O
）,O
、,O
1,O
7,O
6,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
3,O
2,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
6,O
2,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
8,O
8,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
鸡,O
儿,O
岭,O
）,O
、,O
2,O
0,O
1,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
2,O
2,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
2,O
4,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
1,O
9,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
米,O
塘,O
）,O
、,O
1,O
7,O
7,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
9,O
3,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
2,O
0,O
3,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
2,O
7,O
0,O
.,O
4,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
桐,O
油,O
大,O
岭,O
）,O
、,O
1,O
7,O
9,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
2,O
3,O
7,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
3,O
1,O
6,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
0,O
9,O
.,O
4,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
公,O
猪,O
脊,O
）,O
、,O
2,O
9,O
1,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
5,O
2,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
1,O
9,O
2,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
2,O
5,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
大,O
六,O
岭,O
）,O
、,O
2,O
7,O
9,O
.,O
7,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
6,O
1,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
1,O
9,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
立,O
石,O
岭,O
）,O
、,O
4,O
2,O
9,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
0,O
4,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
3,O
3,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
6,O
4,O
9,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
六,O
吉,O
顶,O
）,O
、,O
5,O
7,O
7,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
6,O
6,O
4,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
6,O
5,O
1,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
至,O
6,O
7,O
6,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
五,O
方,O
顶,O
）,O
止,O
。,O
附,O
件,O
2,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
壮,I_ORG
族,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
人,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
关,O
于,O
同,O
意,O
申,O
报,O
设,O
立,O
玉,B_ORG
林,I_ORG
保,I_ORG
税,I_ORG
物,I_ORG
流,I_ORG
中,I_ORG
心,I_ORG
（,O
B,O
型,O
）,O
的,O
批,O
复,O
（,O
桂,O
政,O
函,O
〔,O
2,O
0,O
2,O
1,O
〕,O
9,O
7,O
号,O
）,O
玉,B_ORG
林,I_ORG
市,I_ORG
人,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
：,O
你,O
市,O
关,O
于,O
设,O
立,O
玉,O
林,O
保,O
税,O
物,O
流,O
中,O
心,O
（,O
B,O
型,O
）,O
的,O
请,O
示,O
收,O
悉,O
。,O
现,O
批,O
复,O
如,O
下,O
：,O
同,O
意,O
你,O
市,O
以,O
广,O
西,O
铜,O
州,O
控,O
股,O
有,O
限,O
公,O
司,O
为,O
项,O
目,O
业,O
主,O
，,O
申,O
报,O
设,O
立,O
玉,B_ORG
林,I_ORG
保,I_ORG
税,I_ORG
物,I_ORG
流,I_ORG
中,I_ORG
心,I_ORG
（,O
B,O
型,O
）,O
。,O
该,O
中,O
心,O
选,O
址,O
位,O
于,O
北,B_LOC
流,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
塘,I_LOC
岸,I_LOC
镇,I_LOC
北,I_LOC
侧,I_LOC
广,I_LOC
西,I_LOC
（,I_LOC
北,I_LOC
流,I_LOC
）,I_LOC
轻,I_LOC
工,I_LOC
产,I_LOC
业,I_LOC
园,I_LOC
内,O
，,O
四,O
至,O
范,O
围,O
：,O
东,O
至,O
纵,B_LOC
九,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
、,O
南,O
至,O
横,B_LOC
四,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
、,O
西,O
至,O
纵,B_LOC
一,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
、,O
北,O
至,O
横,B_LOC
三,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
，,O
规,O
划,O
用,O
地,O
面,O
积,O
为,O
1,O
7,O
6,O
.,O
请,O
你,O
市,O
商,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
有,O
关,O
部,O
门,O
指,O
导,O
广,O
西,O
铜,O
州,O
控,O
股,O
有,O
限,O
公,O
司,O
进,O
一,O
步,O
完,O
善,O
《,B_PRO
设,I_PRO
立,I_PRO
玉,I_PRO
林,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
税,I_PRO
物,I_PRO
流,I_PRO
中,I_PRO
心,I_PRO
（,I_PRO
B,I_PRO
型,I_PRO
）,I_PRO
可,I_PRO
行,I_PRO
性,I_PRO
研,I_PRO
究,I_PRO
报,I_PRO
告,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
后,O
，,O
按,O
有,O
关,O
规,O
定,O
报,O
海,O
关,O
部,O
门,O
办,O
理,O
审,O
批,O
手,O
续,O
。,O
现,O
批,O
复,O
如,O
下,O
：,O
一,O
、,O
原,O
则,O
同,O
意,O
在,O
大,O
塘,O
至,O
浦,B_LOC
北,I_LOC
公,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
全,O
线,O
设,O
置,O
长,O
滩,O
、,O
太,B_LOC
平,I_LOC
南,I_LOC
、,O
那,B_LOC
隆,I_LOC
、,O
灵,B_LOC
山,I_LOC
、,O
灵,B_LOC
山,I_LOC
东,I_LOC
5,O
个,O
匝,O
道,O
收,O
费,O
站,O
。,O
三,O
、,O
大,O
塘,O
至,O
浦,B_LOC
北,I_LOC
公,O
路,O
收,O
费,O
期,O
限,O
暂,O
核,O
定,O
3,B_T
年,I_T
，,O
从,O
项,O
目,O
交,O
工,O
验,O
收,O
合,O
格,O
、,O
正,O
式,O
通,O
车,O
之,O
日,O
算,O
起,O
。,O
四,O
、,O
核,O
定,O
大,O
塘,O
至,O
浦,O
北,O
公,O
路,O
收,O
费,O
里,O
程,O
为,O
1,O
2,O
3,O
.,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
壮,I_ORG
族,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
人,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
1,I_T
2,I_T
月,I_T
1,I_T
日,I_T
（,O
此,O
件,O
公,O
开,O
发,O
布,O
）,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
壮,I_ORG
族,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
人,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
办,I_ORG
公,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
关,O
于,O
印,O
发,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
全,O
区,O
推,O
动,O
经,O
济,O
高,O
质,O
量,O
发,O
展,O
和,O
优,O
化,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
情,O
况,O
“,O
红,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
督,O
查,O
通,O
报,O
工,O
作,O
方,O
案,O
的,O
通,O
知,O
（,O
桂,O
政,O
办,O
函,O
〔,O
2,O
0,O
2,O
0,O
〕,O
9,O
号,O
）,O
各,O
市,O
、,O
县,O
人,O
民,O
政,O
府,O
，,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
人,O
民,O
政,O
府,O
各,O
组,O
成,O
部,O
门,O
、,O
各,O
直,O
属,O
机,O
构,O
：,O
《,B_PRO
2,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
2,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
年,I_PRO
全,I_PRO
区,I_PRO
推,I_PRO
动,I_PRO
经,I_PRO
济,I_PRO
高,I_PRO
质,I_PRO
量,I_PRO
发,I_PRO
展,I_PRO
和,I_PRO
优,I_PRO
化,I_PRO
营,I_PRO
商,I_PRO
环,I_PRO
境,I_PRO
情,I_PRO
况,I_PRO
“,I_PRO
红,I_PRO
黑,I_PRO
榜,I_PRO
”,I_PRO
督,I_PRO
查,I_PRO
通,I_PRO
报,I_PRO
工,I_PRO
作,I_PRO
方,I_PRO
案,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
已,O
经,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
人,O
民,O
政,O
府,O
同,O
意,O
，,O
现,O
印,O
发,O
给,O
你,O
们,O
，,O
请,O
认,O
真,O
组,O
织,O
实,O
施,O
。,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
3,I_T
月,I_T
3,I_T
1,I_T
日,I_T
（,O
此,O
件,O
公,O
开,O
发,O
布,O
）,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
全,O
区,O
推,O
动,O
经,O
济,O
高,O
质,O
量,O
发,O
展,O
和,O
优,O
化,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
情,O
况,O
“,O
红,B_PRO
黑,I_PRO
榜,I_PRO
”,O
督,O
查,O
通,O
报,O
工,O
作,O
方,O
案,O
为,O
进,O
一,O
步,O
推,O
动,O
经,O
济,O
高,O
质,O
量,O
发,O
展,O
和,O
优,O
化,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
，,O
根,O
据,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
自,O
治,O
区,O
《,B_PRO
政,I_PRO
府,I_PRO
工,I_PRO
作,I_PRO
报,I_PRO
告,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
的,O
工,O
作,O
部,O
署,O
，,O
决,O
定,O
对,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
全,O
区,O
推,O
动,O
经,O
济,O
高,O
质,O
量,O
发,O
展,O
和,O
优,O
化,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
情,O
况,O
进,O
行,O
“,O
红,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
督,O
查,O
通,O
报,O
。,O
为,O
做,O
好,O
督,O
查,O
通,O
报,O
工,O
作,O
，,O
特,O
制,O
定,O
本,O
方,O
案,O
。,O
一,O
、,O
督,O
查,O
通,O
报,O
内,O
容,O
督,O
查,O
通,O
报,O
指,O
标,O
分,O
为,O
排,O
名,O
通,O
报,O
指,O
标,O
和,O
非,O
排,O
名,O
通,O
报,O
指,O
标,O
两,O
个,O
板,O
块,O
。,O
（,O
一,O
）,O
排,O
名,O
通,O
报,O
指,O
标,O
共,O
2,O
2,O
项,O
。,O
主,O
要,O
是,O
按,O
经,O
济,O
高,O
质,O
量,O
发,O
展,O
和,O
优,O
化,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
要,O
求,O
，,O
由,O
反,O
映,O
经,O
济,O
发,O
展,O
质,O
量,O
效,O
益,O
指,O
标,O
、,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
指,O
标,O
、,O
生,O
态,O
环,O
保,O
指,O
标,O
、,O
政,O
务,O
服,O
务,O
指,O
标,O
等,O
指,O
标,O
构,O
成,O
。,O
排,O
名,O
通,O
报,O
指,O
标,O
类,O
别,O
指,O
标,O
名,O
称,O
周,O
期,O
层,O
级,O
数,O
据,O
提,O
供,O
单,O
位,O
具,O
体,O
设,O
置,O
情,O
况,O
经,O
济,O
发,O
展,O
质,O
量,O
效,O
益,O
指,O
标,O
中,O
央,O
预,O
算,O
内,O
投,O
资,O
项,O
目,O
执,O
行,O
情,O
况,O
：,O
1,O
.,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
、,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
投,O
资,O
计,O
划,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
工,O
率,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
、,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
投,O
资,O
计,O
划,O
项,O
目,O
中,O
央,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
。,O
3,O
.,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
8,I_T
年,I_T
、,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
、,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
投,O
资,O
计,O
划,O
项,O
目,O
中,O
央,O
资,O
金,O
支,O
付,O
率,O
。,O
月,O
度,O
市,O
、,O
县,O
1,O
.,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
发,O
展,O
改,O
革,O
委,O
负,O
责,O
制,O
定,O
开,O
工,O
率,O
和,O
中,O
央,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
年,O
度,O
考,O
评,O
绩,O
效,O
目,O
标,O
并,O
提,O
供,O
月,O
度,O
进,O
度,O
数,O
据,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
财,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
负,O
责,O
制,O
定,O
中,O
央,O
资,O
金,O
支,O
付,O
率,O
年,O
度,O
考,O
评,O
绩,O
效,O
目,O
标,O
并,O
提,O
供,O
月,O
度,O
进,O
度,O
数,O
据,O
。,O
1,O
.,O
以,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
、,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
投,O
资,O
计,O
划,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
工,O
率,O
，,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
、,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
投,O
资,O
计,O
划,O
项,O
目,O
中,O
央,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
，,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
8,I_T
年,I_T
、,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
、,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
投,O
资,O
计,O
划,O
项,O
目,O
中,O
央,O
资,O
金,O
支,O
付,O
率,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
各,O
项,O
指,O
标,O
全,O
区,O
都,O
达,O
到,O
1,O
0,O
0,O
%,O
后,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
3,O
.,O
各,O
项,O
指,O
标,O
达,O
到,O
年,O
度,O
考,O
评,O
绩,O
效,O
目,O
标,O
后,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
4,O
.,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
投,O
资,O
计,O
划,O
项,O
目,O
中,O
央,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
、,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
投,O
资,O
计,O
划,O
项,O
目,O
中,O
央,O
资,O
金,O
支,O
付,O
率,O
从,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
7,I_T
月,I_T
起,O
列,O
“,O
红,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
经,O
济,O
发,O
展,O
质,O
量,O
效,O
益,O
指,O
标,O
投,O
资,O
项,O
目,O
进,O
展,O
信,O
息,O
填,O
报,O
率,O
月,O
度,O
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
发,O
展,O
改,O
革,O
委,O
以,O
投,O
资,O
项,O
目,O
进,O
展,O
信,O
息,O
填,O
报,O
率,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
投,O
资,O
项,O
目,O
进,O
展,O
信,O
息,O
填,O
报,O
率,O
达,O
到,O
9,O
0,O
%,O
以,O
上,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
层,O
面,O
统,O
筹,O
推,O
进,O
重,O
大,O
项,O
目,O
进,O
度,O
：,O
1,O
.,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
层,O
面,O
统,O
筹,O
推,O
进,O
重,O
大,O
项,O
目,O
完,O
成,O
投,O
资,O
同,O
比,O
增,O
长,O
率,O
（,O
市,O
）,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
层,O
面,O
统,O
筹,O
推,O
进,O
重,O
大,O
项,O
目,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
（,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
及,O
企,O
业,O
）,O
。,O
3,O
.,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
层,O
面,O
统,O
筹,O
推,O
进,O
重,O
大,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
工,O
率,O
（,O
市,O
）,O
。,O
4,O
.,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
层,O
面,O
统,O
筹,O
推,O
进,O
重,O
大,O
项,O
目,O
竣,O
工,O
率,O
（,O
市,O
）,O
。,O
月,O
度,O
市,O
，,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
及,O
企,O
业,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
发,O
展,O
改,O
革,O
委,O
以,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
层,O
面,O
统,O
筹,O
推,O
进,O
重,O
大,O
项,O
目,O
完,O
成,O
投,O
资,O
同,O
比,O
增,O
长,O
率,O
、,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
、,O
开,O
工,O
率,O
、,O
竣,O
工,O
率,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
层,O
面,O
统,O
筹,O
推,O
进,O
重,O
大,O
项,O
目,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
达,O
到,O
9,O
0,O
%,O
后,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
3,O
.,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
层,O
面,O
统,O
筹,O
推,O
进,O
重,O
大,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
工,O
率,O
达,O
到,O
8,O
0,O
%,O
后,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
4,O
.,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
层,O
面,O
统,O
筹,O
推,O
进,O
重,O
大,O
项,O
目,O
竣,O
工,O
率,O
达,O
到,O
7,O
0,O
%,O
后,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
“,O
五,O
网,O
”,O
建,O
设,O
大,O
会,O
战,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
实,O
施,O
项,O
目,O
进,O
度,O
：,O
“,O
五,O
网,O
”,O
建,O
设,O
大,O
会,O
战,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
实,O
施,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
工,O
率,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
“,O
五,O
网,O
”,O
建,O
设,O
大,O
会,O
战,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
实,O
施,O
项,O
目,O
年,O
度,O
计,O
划,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
。,O
月,B_ORG
度,I_ORG
市,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
以,O
“,O
五,O
网,O
”,O
建,O
设,O
大,O
会,O
战,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
实,O
施,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
工,O
率,O
、,O
年,O
度,O
计,O
划,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
“,O
五,O
网,O
”,O
建,O
设,O
大,O
会,O
战,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
实,O
施,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
工,O
率,O
、,O
年,O
度,O
计,O
划,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
达,O
到,O
8,O
0,O
%,O
后,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
3,O
.,O
“,O
五,O
网,O
”,O
建,O
设,O
大,O
会,O
战,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
实,O
施,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
工,O
率,O
、,O
年,O
度,O
计,O
划,O
投,O
资,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
从,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
7,I_T
月,I_T
起,O
列,O
“,O
红,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
招,O
商,O
引,O
资,O
重,O
点,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
竣,O
工,O
率,O
季,O
度,O
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
投,O
资,O
促,O
进,O
局,O
以,O
纳,O
入,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
招,O
商,O
引,O
资,O
重,O
点,O
项,O
目,O
清,O
单,O
的,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
竣,O
工,O
率,O
综,O
合,O
测,O
算,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
招,O
商,O
引,O
资,O
重,O
点,O
项,O
目,O
开,O
竣,O
工,O
率,O
达,O
到,O
一,O
定,O
比,O
例,O
（,O
具,O
体,O
待,O
测,O
算,O
）,O
后,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
经,O
济,O
发,O
展,O
质,O
量,O
效,O
益,O
指,O
标,O
新,O
签,O
招,O
商,O
引,O
资,O
5,O
亿,O
元,O
以,O
上,O
产,O
业,O
项,O
目,O
实,O
施,O
率,O
季,O
度,O
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
投,O
资,O
促,O
进,O
局,O
1,O
.,O
以,O
涉,O
及,O
的,O
产,O
业,O
项,O
目,O
投,O
资,O
总,O
额,O
按,O
5,O
亿,O
元,O
—,O
1,O
0,O
亿,O
元,O
、,O
1,O
0,O
亿,O
元,O
—,O
5,O
0,O
亿,O
元,O
、,O
5,O
0,O
亿,O
元,O
以,O
上,O
3,O
个,O
投,O
资,O
额,O
度,O
层,O
级,O
，,O
分,O
权,O
重,O
设,O
置,O
并,O
综,O
合,O
测,O
算,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
全,O
区,O
新,O
签,O
5,O
亿,O
元,O
及,O
以,O
上,O
项,O
目,O
总,O
数,O
低,O
于,O
3,O
0,O
个,O
时,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
小,O
微,O
企,O
业,O
贷,O
款,O
余,O
额,O
增,O
速,O
半,O
年,O
市,O
牵,O
头,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
人,O
民,O
银,O
行,O
南,O
宁,O
中,O
心,O
支,O
行,O
配,O
合,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
银,I_ORG
保,I_ORG
监,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
以,O
小,O
微,O
企,O
业,O
贷,O
款,O
余,O
额,O
增,O
速,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
指,O
标,O
建,O
筑,O
许,O
可,O
办,O
理,O
时,O
间,O
半,O
年,O
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
住,O
房,B_ORG
城,I_ORG
乡,I_ORG
建,I_ORG
设,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
发,B_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
、,O
自,O
然,O
资,O
源,O
厅,O
等,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
工,O
程,O
建,O
设,O
项,O
目,O
审,O
批,O
制,O
度,O
改,O
革,O
领,O
导,O
小,O
组,O
成,O
员,O
单,O
位,O
以,O
建,O
筑,O
许,O
可,O
办,O
理,O
时,O
间,O
由,O
短,O
到,O
长,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
第,O
三,O
方,O
评,O
估,O
在,O
6,O
0,O
个,O
工,O
作,O
日,O
内,O
办,O
结,O
且,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
第,O
三,O
方,O
评,O
估,O
超,O
过,O
6,O
0,O
个,O
工,O
作,O
日,O
办,O
结,O
且,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
建,O
筑,O
许,O
可,O
（,O
社,O
会,O
投,O
资,O
低,O
风,O
险,O
产,O
业,O
类,O
项,O
目,O
审,O
批,O
）,O
办,O
理,O
时,O
间,O
半,O
年,O
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
住,O
房,B_ORG
城,I_ORG
乡,I_ORG
建,I_ORG
设,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
发,B_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
、,O
自,O
然,O
资,O
源,O
厅,O
等,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
工,O
程,O
建,O
设,O
项,O
目,O
审,O
批,O
制,O
度,O
改,O
革,O
领,O
导,O
小,O
组,O
成,O
员,O
单,O
位,O
以,O
建,O
筑,O
许,O
可,O
（,O
社,O
会,O
投,O
资,O
低,O
风,O
险,O
产,O
业,O
类,O
项,O
目,O
审,O
批,O
）,O
办,O
理,O
时,O
间,O
由,O
短,O
到,O
长,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
第,O
三,O
方,O
评,O
估,O
在,O
2,O
3,O
个,O
自,O
然,O
日,O
内,O
办,O
结,O
且,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
第,O
三,O
方,O
评,O
估,O
超,O
过,O
2,O
3,O
个,O
自,O
然,O
日,O
办,O
结,O
且,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
登,O
记,O
财,O
产,O
：,O
企,O
业,O
间,O
不,O
动,O
产,O
转,O
移,O
时,O
间,O
半,O
年,O
市,O
牵,O
头,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
自,O
然,O
资,O
源,O
厅,O
配,O
合,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
住,O
房,B_ORG
城,I_ORG
乡,I_ORG
建,I_ORG
设,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
广,I_ORG
西,I_ORG
税,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
自,O
治,O
区,O
高,O
级,O
法,O
院,O
1,O
.,O
以,O
企,O
业,O
间,O
不,O
动,O
产,O
转,O
移,O
5,O
个,O
抽,O
样,O
平,O
均,O
时,O
间,O
由,O
短,O
到,O
长,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
企,O
业,O
间,O
不,O
动,O
产,O
转,O
移,O
办,O
结,O
时,O
间,O
在,O
0,B_T
.,I_T
5,I_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
以,O
内,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
获,O
得,O
电,O
力,O
：,O
系,O
统,O
平,O
均,O
停,O
电,O
时,O
长,O
指,O
数,O
半,O
年,O
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
工,O
业,O
和,O
信,O
息,O
化,O
厅,O
1,O
.,O
以,O
系,O
统,O
平,O
均,O
停,O
电,O
时,O
长,O
指,O
数,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
系,O
统,O
平,O
均,O
停,O
电,O
时,O
长,O
指,O
数,O
不,O
超,O
过,O
1,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
指,O
标,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
：,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
环,O
节,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
时,O
间,O
。,O
半,B_T
年,I_T
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
住,O
房,O
城,O
乡,O
建,O
设,O
厅,O
1,O
.,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
环,O
节,O
：,O
超,O
过,O
3,O
个,O
环,O
节,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
时,O
间,O
：,O
（,O
1,O
）,O
有,O
外,O
线,O
工,O
程,O
：,O
外,O
线,O
工,O
程,O
（,O
≤,O
5,O
0,O
米,O
）,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
时,O
间,O
从,O
正,O
式,O
受,O
理,O
报,O
装,O
申,O
请,O
到,O
装,O
表,O
通,O
水,O
办,O
理,O
时,O
间,O
不,O
超,O
过,O
9,B_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
（,O
不,O
含,O
办,O
理,O
相,O
关,O
行,O
政,O
审,O
批,O
手,O
续,O
时,O
间,O
）,O
的,O
，,O
以,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
办,O
理,O
时,O
间,O
由,O
短,O
到,O
长,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
外,O
线,O
工,O
程,O
（,O
≤,O
5,O
0,O
米,O
）,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
时,O
间,O
从,O
正,O
式,O
受,O
理,O
报,O
装,O
申,O
请,O
到,O
装,O
表,O
通,O
水,O
办,O
理,O
时,O
间,O
超,O
过,O
9,B_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
（,O
不,O
含,O
办,O
理,O
相,O
关,O
行,O
政,O
审,O
批,O
手,O
续,O
时,O
间,O
）,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
（,O
2,O
）,O
无,O
外,O
线,O
工,O
程,O
：,O
无,O
外,O
线,O
工,O
程,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
时,O
间,O
从,O
正,O
式,O
受,O
理,O
报,O
装,O
申,O
请,O
到,O
装,O
表,O
通,O
水,O
办,O
理,O
时,O
间,O
不,O
超,O
过,O
6,B_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
的,O
，,O
以,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
办,O
理,O
时,O
间,O
由,O
短,O
到,O
长,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
无,O
外,O
线,O
工,O
程,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
水,O
时,O
间,O
从,O
正,O
式,O
受,O
理,O
报,O
装,O
申,O
请,O
到,O
装,O
表,O
通,O
水,O
办,O
理,O
时,O
间,O
超,O
过,O
6,B_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
气,O
：,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
气,O
环,O
节,O
。,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
气,O
时,O
间,O
。,O
3,O
.,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
气,O
办,O
理,O
成,O
本,O
。,O
半,B_T
年,I_T
市,O
牵,O
头,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
住,O
房,O
城,O
乡,O
建,O
设,O
厅,O
配,O
合,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
发,O
展,O
改,O
革,O
委,O
1,O
.,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
气,O
环,O
节,O
：,O
在,O
3,O
个,O
环,O
节,O
以,O
内,O
的,O
，,O
以,O
环,O
节,O
数,O
量,O
由,O
少,O
到,O
多,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
超,O
过,O
3,O
个,O
环,O
节,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
气,O
时,O
间,O
：,O
（,O
1,O
）,O
室,O
内,O
管,O
线,O
工,O
程,O
：,O
在,O
2,B_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
内,I_T
提,O
供,O
方,O
案,O
且,O
6,B_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
内,O
通,O
气,O
的,O
，,O
以,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
气,O
时,O
间,O
由,O
短,O
到,O
长,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
超,O
过,O
2,B_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
提,O
供,O
方,O
案,O
或,O
超,O
过,O
6,B_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
通,O
气,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
（,O
2,O
）,O
室,O
外,O
管,O
线,O
工,O
程,O
（,O
≤,O
3,O
0,O
米,O
）,O
：,O
在,O
3,B_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
内,O
提,O
供,O
方,O
案,O
且,O
1,B_T
1,I_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
内,O
通,O
气,O
的,O
，,O
以,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
气,O
时,O
间,O
由,O
短,O
到,O
长,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
超,O
过,O
3,B_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
提,O
供,O
方,O
案,O
或,O
超,O
过,O
1,B_T
1,I_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
通,O
气,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
3,O
.,O
获,O
得,O
用,O
气,O
办,O
理,O
成,O
本,O
：,O
有,O
办,O
理,O
成,O
本,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
注,O
：,O
办,O
理,O
成,O
本,O
是,O
指,O
建,O
筑,O
安,O
装,O
定,O
额,O
计,O
价,O
之,O
外,O
的,O
开,O
口,O
费,O
、,O
碰,O
口,O
费,O
、,O
押,O
金,O
、,O
保,O
证,O
金,O
等,O
。,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
指,O
标,O
获,O
得,O
信,O
贷,O
：,O
普,O
惠,O
型,O
小,O
微,O
企,O
业,O
贷,O
款,O
综,O
合,O
融,O
资,O
成,O
本,O
半,B_T
年,I_T
市,I_T
牵,I_T
头,I_T
单,I_T
位,I_T
：,I_T
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
银,I_ORG
保,I_ORG
监,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
配,O
合,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
地,O
方,O
金,O
融,O
监,O
管,O
局,O
人,O
民,O
银,O
行,O
南,O
宁,O
中,O
心,O
支,O
行,O
未,O
完,O
成,O
“,O
普,O
惠,O
型,O
小,O
微,O
企,O
业,O
贷,O
款,O
综,O
合,O
融,O
资,O
成,O
本,O
再,O
降,O
0,O
.,O
5,O
个,O
百,O
分,O
点,O
”,O
目,O
标,O
任,O
务,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
跨,O
境,O
贸,O
易,O
：,O
进,O
出,O
口,O
通,O
关,O
时,O
间,O
半,B_T
年,I_T
市,O
牵,O
头,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
南,B_ORG
宁,I_ORG
海,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
配,O
合,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
商,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
（,O
口,O
岸,O
办,O
）,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
交,I_ORG
通,I_ORG
运,I_ORG
输,B_ORG
厅,I_ORG
广,I_ORG
西,I_ORG
海,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
局,B_ORG
广,I_ORG
西,I_ORG
出,I_ORG
入,I_ORG
境,I_ORG
边,B_ORG
防,I_ORG
检,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
总,I_ORG
站,I_ORG
沿,O
海,O
口,O
岸,O
进,O
口,O
整,O
体,O
通,O
关,O
时,O
间,O
较,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
压,O
缩,O
1,O
0,O
%,O
以,O
上,O
（,O
含,O
1,O
0,O
%,O
),O
、,O
出,O
口,O
整,O
体,O
通,O
关,O
时,O
间,O
优,O
于,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
水,O
平,O
，,O
其,O
他,O
口,O
岸,O
进,O
口,O
、,O
出,O
口,O
整,O
体,O
通,O
关,O
时,O
间,O
均,O
优,O
于,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
水,O
平,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
所,O
有,O
口,O
岸,O
进,O
口,O
、,O
出,O
口,O
整,O
体,O
通,O
关,O
时,O
间,O
比,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
长,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
执,O
行,O
合,O
同,O
：,O
解,O
决,O
商,O
业,O
纠,O
纷,O
时,O
间,O
半,B_T
年,I_T
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
高,O
级,O
法,O
院,O
以,O
解,O
决,O
商,O
业,O
纠,O
纷,O
5,O
个,O
抽,O
样,O
平,O
均,O
时,O
间,O
由,O
短,O
到,O
长,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
注,O
：,O
抽,O
样,O
范,O
围,O
为,O
各,O
市,O
中,O
级,O
法,O
院,O
涉,O
企,O
业,O
合,O
同,O
纠,O
纷,O
一,O
审,O
审,O
结,O
生,O
效,O
且,O
进,O
入,O
执,O
行,O
程,O
序,O
的,O
案,O
件,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
解,O
决,O
商,O
业,O
纠,O
纷,O
办,O
结,O
时,O
间,O
少,O
于,O
3,B_T
3,I_T
0,I_T
天,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
办,O
理,O
破,O
产,O
：,O
债,O
权,O
人,O
回,O
收,O
率,O
半,O
年,O
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
高,O
级,O
法,O
院,O
1,O
.,O
以,O
债,O
权,O
人,O
回,O
收,O
2,O
个,O
抽,O
样,O
平,O
均,O
回,O
收,O
率,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
债,O
权,O
人,O
回,O
收,O
率,O
高,O
于,O
4,O
5,O
%,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
基,O
本,O
公,O
共,O
服,O
务,O
：,O
每,O
千,O
老,O
年,O
人,O
口,O
养,O
老,O
床,O
位,O
数,O
半,B_T
年,I_T
市,B_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
1,O
.,O
以,O
每,O
千,O
老,O
年,O
人,O
口,O
养,O
老,O
床,O
位,O
数,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
每,O
千,O
老,O
年,O
人,O
口,O
养,O
老,O
床,O
位,O
数,O
高,O
于,O
2,O
5,O
张,O
/,O
千,O
人,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
基,O
本,O
公,O
共,O
服,O
务,O
：,O
农,O
村,O
特,O
困,O
人,O
员,O
供,O
养,O
服,O
务,O
机,O
构,O
法,O
人,O
登,O
记,O
率,O
半,B_T
年,I_T
市,B_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
以,O
农,O
村,O
特,O
困,O
人,O
员,O
供,O
养,O
服,O
务,O
机,O
构,O
法,O
人,O
登,O
记,O
率,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
农,O
村,O
特,O
困,O
人,O
员,O
供,O
养,O
服,O
务,O
机,O
构,O
法,O
人,O
登,O
记,O
率,O
高,O
于,O
9,O
0,O
%,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
生,O
态,O
环,O
保,O
指,O
标,O
环,O
境,O
空,O
气,O
质,O
量,O
优,O
良,O
天,O
数,O
比,O
率,O
和,O
细,O
颗,O
粒,O
物,O
（,O
P,O
M,O
2,O
.,O
5,O
）,O
平,O
均,O
浓,O
度,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
月,O
度,O
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
生,O
态,O
环,O
境,O
厅,O
1,O
.,O
以,O
环,O
境,O
空,O
气,O
质,O
量,O
优,O
良,O
天,O
数,O
比,O
率,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
（,O
以,O
下,O
简,O
称,O
优,O
良,O
天,O
数,O
比,O
率,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
）,O
＋,O
P,O
M,O
2,O
.,O
5,O
平,O
均,O
浓,O
度,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
出,O
现,O
多,O
个,O
城,O
市,O
目,O
标,O
总,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
相,O
同,O
时,O
，,O
顺,O
次,O
参,O
考,O
P,O
M,O
2,O
.,O
5,O
平,O
均,O
浓,O
度,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
、,O
优,O
良,O
天,O
数,O
比,O
率,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
进,O
行,O
测,O
算,O
。,O
注,O
：,O
优,O
良,O
天,O
数,O
比,O
率,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
,O
1,B_T
月,I_T
至,I_T
X,I_T
月,I_T
实,O
际,O
优,O
良,O
天,O
数,O
÷,O
（,O
优,O
良,O
天,O
数,O
比,O
率,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
×,O
3,B_T
6,I_T
6,I_T
天,I_T
）,O
。,O
P,O
M,O
2,O
.,O
5,O
平,O
均,O
浓,O
度,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
,O
（,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
浓,O
度,O
－,O
1,B_T
月,I_T
至,I_T
X,I_T
月,I_T
平,O
均,O
浓,O
度,O
）,O
÷,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
浓,O
度,O
＋,O
1,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
优,O
良,O
天,O
数,O
比,O
率,O
和,O
P,O
M,O
2,O
.,O
5,O
平,O
均,O
浓,O
度,O
两,O
项,O
指,O
标,O
均,O
优,O
于,O
年,O
度,O
目,O
标,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
政,O
务,O
服,O
务,O
指,O
标,O
政,O
务,O
服,O
务,O
“,O
好,O
差,O
评,O
”,O
评,O
价,O
满,O
意,O
度,O
年,O
度,O
市,O
，,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
大,O
数,O
据,O
发,O
展,O
局,O
1,O
.,O
以,O
政,O
务,O
服,O
务,O
“,O
好,O
差,O
评,O
”,O
评,O
价,O
满,O
意,O
度,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
其,O
中,O
，,O
市,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
5,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
5,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
政,O
务,O
服,O
务,O
“,O
好,O
差,O
评,O
”,O
评,O
价,O
满,O
意,O
度,O
高,O
于,O
9,O
5,O
%,O
（,O
含,O
）,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
政,O
务,O
数,O
据,O
“,O
聚,O
通,O
用,O
”,O
检,O
查,O
结,O
果,O
：,O
政,O
务,O
数,O
据,O
“,O
聚,O
通,O
用,O
”,O
数,O
据,O
治,O
理,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
。,O
2,O
.,O
政,O
务,O
数,O
据,O
“,O
聚,O
通,O
用,O
”,O
检,O
查,O
评,O
估,O
总,O
分,O
。,O
月,O
度,O
市,O
，,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
大,O
数,O
据,O
发,O
展,O
局,O
以,O
政,O
务,O
数,O
据,O
“,O
聚,O
通,O
用,O
”,O
数,O
据,O
治,O
理,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
、,O
检,O
查,O
评,O
估,O
总,O
分,O
分,O
别,O
由,O
高,O
到,O
低,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
其,O
中,O
，,O
市,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
分,O
为,O
三,O
类,O
分,O
别,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
每,O
类,O
排,O
名,O
前,O
5,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
，,O
排,O
名,O
后,O
5,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
列,O
入,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
政,O
务,O
数,O
据,O
“,O
聚,O
通,O
用,O
”,O
数,O
据,O
治,O
理,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
小,O
于,O
7,O
0,O
%,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
；,O
政,O
务,O
数,O
据,O
“,O
聚,O
通,O
用,O
”,O
检,O
查,O
评,O
估,O
总,O
分,O
大,O
于,O
或,O
等,O
于,O
8,O
0,O
分,O
的,O
，,O
不,O
列,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
注,O
：,O
政,O
务,O
数,O
据,O
“,O
聚,O
通,O
用,O
”,O
数,O
据,O
治,O
理,O
完,O
成,O
率,O
、,O
检,O
查,O
评,O
估,O
总,O
分,O
计,O
算,O
方,O
式,O
详,O
见,O
《,B_PRO
广,I_PRO
西,I_PRO
政,I_PRO
务,I_PRO
数,I_PRO
据,I_PRO
资,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
管,I_PRO
理,I_PRO
与,I_PRO
应,I_PRO
用,I_PRO
改,I_PRO
革,I_PRO
2,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
2,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
年,I_PRO
评,I_PRO
估,I_PRO
指,I_PRO
标,I_PRO
说,I_PRO
明,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
。,O
（,O
二,O
）,O
非,O
排,O
名,O
通,O
报,O
指,O
标,O
共,O
1,O
6,O
项,O
。,O
主,O
要,O
由,O
地,O
区,O
生,O
产,O
总,O
值,O
增,O
速,O
（,O
含,O
三,O
次,O
产,O
业,O
增,O
速,O
）,O
、,O
固,O
定,O
资,O
产,O
投,O
资,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
5,O
0,O
0,O
0,O
万,O
元,O
以,O
上,O
项,O
目,O
投,O
资,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
5,O
0,O
0,O
万,O
元,O
—,O
5,O
0,O
0,O
0,O
万,O
元,O
项,O
目,O
投,O
资,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
规,O
模,O
以,O
上,O
工,O
业,O
增,O
加,O
值,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
规,O
模,O
以,O
上,O
企,O
业,O
上,O
规,O
入,O
统,O
数,O
量,O
、,O
进,O
出,O
口,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
存,O
贷,O
款,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
社,O
会,O
消,O
费,O
品,O
零,O
售,O
总,O
额,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
规,O
模,O
以,O
上,O
工,O
业,O
高,O
技,O
术,O
产,O
业,O
总,O
产,O
值,O
占,O
全,O
部,O
规,O
模,O
以,O
上,O
工,O
业,O
总,O
产,O
值,O
比,O
重,O
、,O
工,O
业,O
技,O
改,O
投,O
资,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
民,O
间,O
投,O
资,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
城,O
镇,O
居,O
民,O
人,O
均,O
可,O
支,O
配,O
收,O
入,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
农,O
村,O
居,O
民,O
人,O
均,O
可,O
支,O
配,O
收,O
入,O
增,O
速,O
、,O
研,O
发,O
经,O
费,O
支,O
出,O
占,O
地,O
区,O
生,O
产,O
总,O
值,O
比,O
重,O
、,O
高,O
新,O
技,O
术,O
企,O
业,O
保,O
有,O
量,O
等,O
指,O
标,O
构,O
成,O
。,O
非,O
排,O
名,O
通,O
报,O
指,O
标,O
指,O
标,O
名,O
称,O
周,O
期,O
层,O
级,O
数,O
据,O
提,O
供,O
单,O
位,O
地,O
区,O
生,O
产,O
总,O
值,O
增,O
速,O
（,O
含,O
三,O
次,O
产,O
业,O
增,O
速,O
）,O
季,O
度,O
市,O
、,O
县,B_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
固,O
定,O
资,O
产,O
投,O
资,O
增,O
速,O
月,O
度,O
市,O
、,O
县,B_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
5,O
0,O
0,O
0,O
万,O
元,O
以,O
上,O
项,O
目,O
投,O
资,O
增,O
速,O
月,O
度,O
5,O
0,O
0,O
万,O
元,O
—,O
5,O
0,O
0,O
0,O
万,O
元,O
项,O
目,O
投,O
资,O
增,O
速,O
月,O
度,O
规,O
模,O
以,O
上,O
工,O
业,O
增,O
加,O
值,O
增,O
速,O
月,O
度,O
市,B_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
季,O
度,O
县,O
规,O
模,O
以,O
上,O
企,O
业,O
上,O
规,O
入,O
统,O
数,O
量,O
（,O
具,O
体,O
包,O
括,O
：,O
规,O
模,O
以,O
上,O
工,O
业,O
企,O
业,O
、,O
资,O
质,O
内,O
建,O
筑,O
业,O
和,O
房,O
地,O
产,O
开,O
发,O
经,O
营,O
企,O
业,O
、,O
限,O
额,O
以,O
上,O
批,O
发,O
零,O
售,O
住,O
宿,O
企,O
业,O
和,O
规,O
模,O
以,O
上,O
服,O
务,O
业,O
企,O
业,O
）,O
季,B_ORG
度,I_ORG
市,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
进,O
出,O
口,O
增,O
速,O
月,O
度,O
市,O
牵,O
头,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
商,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
配,O
合,O
单,O
位,O
：,O
南,B_ORG
宁,I_ORG
海,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
存,O
贷,O
款,O
增,O
速,O
月,O
度,O
市,B_ORG
人,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
银,I_ORG
行,I_ORG
南,I_ORG
宁,I_ORG
中,I_ORG
心,I_ORG
支,I_ORG
行,I_ORG
社,O
会,O
消,O
费,O
品,O
零,O
售,O
总,O
额,O
增,O
速,O
季,B_ORG
度,I_ORG
市,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
规,O
模,O
以,O
上,O
工,O
业,O
高,O
技,O
术,O
产,O
业,O
总,O
产,O
值,O
占,O
全,O
部,O
规,O
模,O
以,O
上,O
工,O
业,O
总,O
产,O
值,O
比,O
重,O
季,B_ORG
度,I_ORG
市,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
工,I_ORG
业,I_ORG
技,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
投,I_ORG
资,I_ORG
增,I_ORG
速,I_ORG
月,I_ORG
度,I_ORG
市,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
民,O
间,O
投,O
资,O
增,O
速,O
月,O
度,O
市,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
城,O
镇,O
居,O
民,O
人,O
均,O
可,O
支,O
配,O
收,O
入,O
增,O
速,O
季,B_ORG
度,I_ORG
市,I_ORG
国,I_ORG
家,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
广,I_ORG
西,I_ORG
调,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
总,I_ORG
队,I_ORG
农,O
村,O
居,O
民,O
人,O
均,O
可,O
支,O
配,O
收,O
入,O
增,O
速,O
季,B_ORG
度,I_ORG
市,I_ORG
国,I_ORG
家,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
广,I_ORG
西,I_ORG
调,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
总,I_ORG
队,I_ORG
研,O
发,O
经,O
费,O
支,O
出,O
占,O
地,O
区,O
生,O
产,O
总,O
值,O
比,O
重,O
年,O
度,B_ORG
市,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
高,O
新,O
技,O
术,O
企,O
业,O
保,O
有,O
量,O
半,B_T
年,I_T
市,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
科,O
技,O
厅,O
二,O
、,O
督,O
查,O
通,O
报,O
形,O
式,O
（,O
一,O
）,O
以,O
《,B_PRO
全,I_PRO
区,I_PRO
推,I_PRO
动,I_PRO
经,I_PRO
济,I_PRO
高,I_PRO
质,I_PRO
量,I_PRO
发,I_PRO
展,I_PRO
和,I_PRO
优,I_PRO
化,I_PRO
营,I_PRO
商,I_PRO
环,I_PRO
境,I_PRO
情,I_PRO
况,I_PRO
“,I_PRO
红,I_PRO
黑,I_PRO
榜,I_PRO
”,I_PRO
督,I_PRO
查,I_PRO
通,I_PRO
报,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
形,O
式,O
进,O
行,O
通,O
报,O
。,O
由,O
于,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
第,I_T
一,I_T
季,I_T
度,I_T
我,O
区,O
经,O
济,O
社,O
会,O
发,O
展,O
受,O
新,O
冠,O
肺,O
炎,O
疫,O
情,O
影,O
响,O
，,O
第,O
一,O
季,O
度,O
各,O
项,O
指,O
标,O
不,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
通,O
报,O
，,O
只,O
进,O
行,O
非,O
排,O
名,O
通,O
报,O
。,O
（,O
二,O
）,O
排,O
名,O
通,O
报,O
指,O
标,O
中,O
涉,O
及,O
各,O
县,O
（,O
市,O
、,O
区,O
）,O
的,O
，,O
根,O
据,O
不,O
同,O
主,O
体,O
功,O
能,O
区,O
定,O
位,O
，,O
分,O
类,O
进,O
行,O
排,O
名,O
。,O
各,O
县,O
（,O
市,O
、,O
区,O
）,O
按,O
照,O
重,O
点,O
开,O
发,O
区,O
、,O
农,O
产,O
品,O
主,O
产,O
区,O
、,O
重,O
点,O
生,O
态,O
功,O
能,O
区,O
、,O
城,O
市,O
主,O
城,O
区,O
分,O
类,O
排,O
名,O
，,O
并,O
确,O
定,O
“,O
红,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
。,O
（,O
三,O
）,O
排,O
名,O
通,O
报,O
指,O
标,O
涉,O
及,O
的,O
相,O
关,O
指,O
标,O
整,O
体,O
数,O
据,O
作,O
为,O
附,O
件,O
一,O
并,O
通,O
报,O
。,O
三,O
、,O
督,O
查,O
通,O
报,O
呈,O
报,O
及,O
分,O
送,O
、,O
抄,O
送,O
范,O
围,O
（,O
一,O
）,O
呈,O
报,O
：,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
党,O
委,O
书,O
记,O
、,O
副,O
书,O
记,O
、,O
常,O
委,O
，,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
人,O
大,O
常,O
委,O
会,O
主,O
任,O
、,O
副,O
主,O
任,O
，,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
主,O
席,O
、,O
副,O
主,O
席,O
，,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
政,O
协,O
主,O
席,O
、,O
副,O
主,O
席,O
，,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
人,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
秘,O
书,O
长,O
，,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
党,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
、,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
人,O
民,O
政,O
府,O
副,O
秘,O
书,O
长,O
，,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
党,O
委,O
办,O
公,O
厅,O
、,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
政,O
府,O
办,O
公,O
厅,O
领,O
导,O
。,O
（,O
二,O
）,O
分,O
送,O
：,O
全,O
区,O
各,O
市,O
、,O
县,O
（,O
市,O
、,O
区,O
）,O
党,O
政,O
主,O
要,O
负,O
责,O
人,O
，,O
区,O
直,O
、,O
中,O
直,O
有,O
关,O
部,O
门,O
主,O
要,O
负,O
责,O
人,O
。,O
（,O
三,O
）,O
抄,O
送,O
：,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
党,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
办,I_ORG
公,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
，,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
党,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
组,I_ORG
织,I_ORG
部,I_ORG
，,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
党,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
研,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
，,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
党,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
，,O
各,O
市,O
党,O
委,O
组,O
织,O
部,O
，,O
各,O
市,O
、,O
县,O
（,O
市,O
、,O
区,O
）,O
政,O
府,O
办,O
公,O
室,O
，,O
各,O
市,O
、,O
县,O
（,O
市,O
、,O
区,O
）,O
政,O
府,O
督,O
查,O
机,O
构,O
。,O
四,O
、,O
督,O
查,O
通,O
报,O
工,O
作,O
分,O
工,O
要,O
求,O
（,O
一,O
）,O
收,O
集,O
汇,O
总,O
。,O
由,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
高,O
级,O
法,O
院,O
，,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
教,I_ORG
育,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
科,O
技,O
厅,O
、,O
工,B_ORG
业,I_ORG
和,I_ORG
信,I_ORG
息,I_ORG
化,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
民,O
政,O
厅,O
、,O
财,O
政,O
厅,O
、,O
自,O
然,O
资,O
源,O
厅,O
、,O
生,O
态,O
环,O
境,O
厅,O
、,O
住,O
房,O
城,O
乡,O
建,O
设,O
厅,O
、,O
交,O
通,O
运,O
输,O
厅,O
、,O
商,O
务,O
厅,O
、,O
市,O
场,O
监,O
管,O
局,O
、,O
统,O
计,O
局,O
、,O
地,O
方,O
金,O
融,O
监,O
管,O
局,O
、,O
大,B_ORG
数,I_ORG
据,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
、,O
投,O
资,O
促,O
进,O
局,O
，,O
人,O
民,O
银,O
行,O
南,O
宁,O
中,O
心,O
支,O
行,O
，,O
南,B_ORG
宁,I_ORG
海,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
，,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
税,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
，,O
国,B_ORG
家,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
调,O
查,O
总,O
队,O
，,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
银,I_ORG
保,I_ORG
监,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
，,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
海,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
，,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
出,I_ORG
入,I_ORG
境,I_ORG
边,I_ORG
防,I_ORG
检,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
总,I_ORG
站,I_ORG
等,O
单,O
位,O
负,O
责,O
采,O
集,O
指,O
标,O
数,O
据,O
（,O
提,O
供,O
的,O
数,O
据,O
为,O
上,O
月,O
度,O
、,O
上,O
季,O
度,O
、,O
上,B_T
半,I_T
年,I_T
、,O
下,B_T
半,I_T
年,I_T
、,O
年,O
度,O
数,O
据,O
）,O
，,O
每,O
项,O
指,O
标,O
的,O
牵,O
头,O
单,O
位,O
按,O
照,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
政,O
府,O
督,O
查,O
室,O
设,O
定,O
的,O
通,O
报,O
模,O
板,O
将,O
数,O
据,O
汇,O
总,O
形,O
成,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
，,O
按,O
时,O
报,O
送,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
发,O
展,O
改,O
革,O
委,O
。,O
（,O
月,O
度,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
于,O
每,O
月,O
2,B_T
3,I_T
日,I_T
前,O
；,O
季,O
度,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
于,O
4,B_T
月,I_T
、,O
7,B_T
月,I_T
、,O
1,B_T
0,I_T
月,I_T
、,O
次,B_T
年,I_T
1,I_T
月,I_T
2,I_T
3,I_T
日,I_T
前,I_T
；,O
半,B_T
年,I_T
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
于,O
7,B_T
月,I_T
、,O
次,B_T
年,I_T
1,I_T
月,I_T
2,I_T
3,I_T
日,I_T
前,I_T
；,O
年,O
度,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
于,O
次,B_T
年,I_T
1,I_T
月,I_T
2,I_T
3,I_T
日,I_T
前,I_T
；,O
研,O
发,O
经,O
费,O
支,O
出,O
占,O
地,O
区,O
生,O
产,O
总,O
值,O
比,O
重,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
于,O
1,B_T
0,I_T
月,I_T
2,I_T
3,I_T
日,I_T
前,O
报,O
送,O
）,O
。,O
（,O
二,O
）,O
审,O
核,O
分,O
析,O
。,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
接,O
到,O
各,O
单,O
位,O
报,O
送,O
的,O
相,O
关,O
指,O
标,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
后,O
，,O
对,O
总,O
体,O
情,O
况,O
进,O
行,O
分,O
析,O
，,O
形,O
成,O
总,O
体,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
，,O
于,O
每,O
月,O
2,B_T
5,I_T
日,I_T
前,O
报,O
送,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
。,O
（,O
三,O
）,O
印,O
发,O
通,O
报,O
。,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
按,O
程,O
序,O
办,O
理,O
总,O
体,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
，,O
经,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
人,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
领,O
导,O
同,O
志,O
审,O
定,O
后,O
以,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
名,O
义,O
印,O
发,O
通,O
报,O
。,O
（,O
四,O
）,O
印,O
前,O
核,O
校,O
。,O
通,O
报,O
的,O
数,O
据,O
、,O
内,O
容,O
由,O
数,O
据,O
提,O
供,O
单,O
位,O
各,O
负,O
其,O
责,O
。,O
在,O
每,O
期,O
通,O
报,O
印,O
前,O
由,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
高,O
级,O
法,O
院,O
，,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
、,O
教,B_ORG
育,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
科,B_ORG
技,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
工,B_ORG
业,I_ORG
和,I_ORG
信,I_ORG
息,I_ORG
化,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
民,B_ORG
政,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
财,O
政,O
厅,O
、,O
自,B_ORG
然,I_ORG
资,I_ORG
源,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
生,B_ORG
态,I_ORG
环,I_ORG
境,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
住,B_ORG
房,I_ORG
城,I_ORG
乡,I_ORG
建,I_ORG
设,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
交,B_ORG
通,I_ORG
运,I_ORG
输,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
商,B_ORG
务,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
市,B_ORG
场,I_ORG
监,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
、,O
统,B_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
、,O
地,B_ORG
方,I_ORG
金,I_ORG
融,I_ORG
监,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
、,O
大,B_ORG
数,I_ORG
据,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
、,O
投,B_ORG
资,I_ORG
促,I_ORG
进,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
，,O
人,O
民,O
银,O
行,O
南,O
宁,O
中,O
心,O
支,O
行,O
，,O
南,B_ORG
宁,I_ORG
海,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
，,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
税,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
，,O
国,B_ORG
家,I_ORG
统,I_ORG
计,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
调,O
查,O
总,O
队,O
，,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
银,I_ORG
保,I_ORG
监,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
，,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
海,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
，,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
出,I_ORG
入,I_ORG
境,I_ORG
边,I_ORG
防,I_ORG
检,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
总,I_ORG
站,I_ORG
分,O
别,O
派,O
相,O
关,O
负,O
责,O
同,O
志,O
到,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
政,O
府,O
督,O
查,O
室,O
，,O
对,O
本,O
单,O
位,O
提,O
供,O
的,O
数,O
据,O
进,O
行,O
核,O
校,O
并,O
签,O
字,O
确,O
认,O
。,O
五,O
、,O
绩,O
效,O
考,O
评,O
将,O
全,O
区,O
推,O
动,O
经,O
济,O
高,O
质,O
量,O
发,O
展,O
和,O
优,O
化,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
情,O
况,O
“,O
红,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
督,O
查,O
通,O
报,O
工,O
作,O
纳,O
入,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
办,I_ORG
公,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
对,O
各,O
市,O
、,O
各,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
度,I_T
绩,O
效,O
考,O
评,O
范,O
围,O
。,O
（,O
一,O
）,O
将,O
各,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
材,O
料,O
数,O
据,O
迟,O
报,O
情,O
况,O
纳,O
入,O
绩,O
效,O
考,O
评,O
，,O
凡,O
是,O
不,O
按,O
时,O
报,O
送,O
的,O
，,O
每,O
次,O
扣,O
0,O
.,O
0,O
5,O
分,O
。,O
各,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
报,O
送,O
给,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
的,O
迟,O
报,O
情,O
况,O
，,O
由,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
统,O
计,O
，,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
每,O
季,O
度,O
汇,O
总,O
一,O
次,O
，,O
并,O
在,O
季,O
度,O
结,O
束,O
后,O
1,B_T
0,I_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
内,I_T
将,O
迟,O
报,O
情,O
况,O
报,O
送,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
，,O
由,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
审,O
核,O
考,O
评,O
。,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
报,O
送,O
给,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
总,O
体,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
的,O
迟,O
报,O
情,O
况,O
，,O
由,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
统,O
计,O
。,O
（,O
二,O
）,O
将,O
各,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
差,O
错,O
情,O
况,O
纳,O
入,O
绩,O
效,O
考,O
评,O
，,O
每,O
出,O
现,O
1,O
次,O
差,O
错,O
扣,O
0,O
.,O
1,O
分,O
。,O
各,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
报,O
送,O
给,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
的,O
差,O
错,O
情,O
况,O
，,O
由,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
统,O
计,O
；,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
报,O
送,O
给,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
总,O
体,O
通,O
报,O
文,O
稿,O
的,O
差,O
错,O
情,O
况,O
，,O
由,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
统,O
计,O
。,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
改,I_ORG
革,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
每,O
季,O
度,O
汇,O
总,O
一,O
次,O
，,O
并,O
在,O
季,O
度,O
结,O
束,O
后,O
1,B_T
0,I_T
个,I_T
工,I_T
作,I_T
日,I_T
内,I_T
将,O
差,O
错,O
情,O
况,O
报,O
送,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
，,O
由,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
督,I_ORG
查,I_ORG
室,I_ORG
审,O
核,O
考,O
评,O
。,O
（,O
三,O
）,O
将,O
各,O
市,O
“,O
红,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
年,O
度,O
排,O
名,O
情,O
况,O
纳,O
入,O
绩,O
效,O
考,O
评,O
。,O
对,O
各,O
市,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
通,O
报,O
年,O
度,O
总,O
次,O
数,O
排,O
名,O
为,O
第,O
1,O
—,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
分,O
别,O
给,O
予,O
绩,O
效,O
加,O
分,O
0,O
.,O
5,O
分,O
；,O
第,O
4,O
—,O
1,O
1,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
分,O
别,O
给,O
予,O
绩,O
效,O
加,O
分,O
0,O
.,O
3,O
分,O
。,O
对,O
各,O
市,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
通,O
报,O
年,O
度,O
总,O
次,O
数,O
排,O
名,O
为,O
第,O
1,O
—,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
分,O
别,O
给,O
予,O
绩,O
效,O
扣,O
分,O
0,O
.,O
3,O
分,O
；,O
第,O
4,O
—,O
1,O
1,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
分,O
别,O
给,O
予,O
绩,O
效,O
扣,O
分,O
0,O
.,O
2,O
分,O
。,O
（,O
四,O
）,O
将,O
各,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
“,O
红,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
年,O
度,O
排,O
名,O
情,O
况,O
纳,O
入,O
绩,O
效,O
考,O
评,O
。,O
对,O
各,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
“,O
红,O
榜,O
”,O
通,O
报,O
年,O
度,O
总,O
次,O
数,O
排,O
名,O
为,O
第,O
1,O
—,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
分,O
别,O
给,O
予,O
绩,O
效,O
加,O
分,O
0,O
.,O
5,O
分,O
；,O
第,O
4,O
—,O
8,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
分,O
别,O
给,O
予,O
绩,O
效,O
加,O
分,O
0,O
.,O
3,O
分,O
。,O
对,O
各,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
“,O
黑,O
榜,O
”,O
通,O
报,O
年,O
度,O
总,O
次,O
数,O
排,O
名,O
为,O
第,O
1,O
—,O
3,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
分,O
别,O
给,O
予,O
绩,O
效,O
扣,O
分,O
0,O
.,O
3,O
分,O
；,O
第,O
4,O
—,O
8,O
名,O
的,O
，,O
分,O
别,O
给,O
予,O
绩,O
效,O
扣,O
分,O
0,O
.,O
2,O
分,O
。,O
（,O
五,O
）,O
对,O
承,O
担,O
通,O
报,O
数,O
据,O
统,O
计,O
工,O
作,O
的,O
各,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
，,O
在,O
年,O
度,O
绩,O
效,O
考,O
评,O
中,O
按,O
有,O
关,O
规,O
定,O
给,O
予,O
加,O
分,O
。,O
现,O
批,O
复,O
如,O
下,O
：,O
一,O
、,O
同,O
意,O
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
银,I_LOC
殿,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
自,I_LOC
治,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
级,I_LOC
自,I_LOC
然,I_LOC
保,I_LOC
护,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
（,O
以,O
下,O
简,O
称,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
）,O
功,O
能,O
区,O
划,O
。,O
现,O
批,O
复,O
如,O
下,O
：,O
一,O
、,O
同,O
意,O
设,O
立,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
级,O
防,O
城,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
、,O
靖,O
西,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
、,O
龙,O
州,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
。,O
防,O
城,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
用,O
地,O
面,O
积,O
6,O
7,O
.,O
0,O
8,O
公,O
顷,O
，,O
靖,O
西,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
用,O
地,O
面,O
积,O
1,O
5,O
2,O
.,O
2,O
9,O
公,O
顷,O
，,O
龙,O
州,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
用,O
地,O
面,O
积,O
4,O
2,O
3,O
.,O
2,O
3,O
公,O
顷,O
。,O
各,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
区,O
域,O
范,O
围,O
为,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
商,O
务,O
厅,O
组,O
织,O
审,O
核,O
确,O
定,O
的,O
四,O
至,O
范,O
围,O
。,O
二,O
、,O
防,B_LOC
城,I_LOC
港,I_LOC
、,O
百,B_LOC
色,I_LOC
、,O
崇,B_LOC
左,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
要,O
切,O
实,O
加,O
强,O
对,O
所,O
辖,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
建,O
设,O
的,O
组,O
织,O
领,O
导,O
，,O
贯,O
彻,O
落,O
实,O
好,O
国,O
家,O
、,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
关,O
于,O
促,O
进,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
高,O
质,O
量,O
发,O
展,O
的,O
相,O
关,O
政,O
策,O
举,O
措,O
，,O
整,O
合,O
资,O
源,O
、,O
加,O
大,O
投,O
入,O
，,O
聚,O
焦,O
特,O
色,O
优,O
势,O
产,O
业,O
，,O
突,O
出,O
创,O
新,O
驱,O
动,O
，,O
全,O
面,O
提,O
升,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
综,O
合,O
发,O
展,O
水,O
平,O
及,O
竞,O
争,O
力,O
，,O
切,O
实,O
将,O
其,O
打,O
造,O
成,O
为,O
集,O
边,O
境,O
贸,O
易,O
、,O
加,O
工,O
制,O
造,O
、,O
生,O
产,O
服,O
务,O
、,O
跨,O
境,O
金,O
融,O
、,O
物,O
流,O
采,O
购,O
为,O
一,O
体,O
的,O
高,O
水,O
平,O
沿,O
边,O
开,O
放,O
平,O
台,O
。,O
三,O
、,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
商,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
要,O
会,O
同,O
有,O
关,O
单,O
位,O
加,O
强,O
指,O
导,O
和,O
服,O
务,O
，,O
促,O
进,O
各,O
边,O
境,O
经,O
济,O
合,O
作,O
区,O
健,O
康,O
快,O
速,O
发,O
展,O
。,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
1,I_T
9,I_T
年,I_T
8,I_T
月,I_T
1,I_T
日,I_T
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
深,O
化,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
整,O
合,O
共,O
享,O
实,O
施,O
方,O
案,O
根,O
据,O
《,B_PRO
国,I_PRO
务,I_PRO
院,I_PRO
办,I_PRO
公,I_PRO
厅,I_PRO
转,I_PRO
发,I_PRO
国,I_PRO
家,I_PRO
发,I_PRO
展,I_PRO
改,I_PRO
革,I_PRO
委,I_PRO
关,I_PRO
于,I_PRO
深,I_PRO
化,I_PRO
公,I_PRO
共,I_PRO
资,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
交,I_PRO
易,I_PRO
平,I_PRO
台,I_PRO
整,I_PRO
合,I_PRO
共,I_PRO
享,I_PRO
指,I_PRO
导,I_PRO
意,I_PRO
见,I_PRO
的,I_PRO
通,I_PRO
知,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
（,O
国,O
办,O
函,O
〔,O
2,O
0,O
1,O
9,O
〕,O
4,O
1,O
号,O
）,O
要,O
求,O
，,O
结,O
合,O
我,O
区,O
实,O
际,O
，,O
制,O
定,O
本,O
方,O
案,O
。,O
一,O
、,O
总,O
体,O
目,O
标,O
到,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
底,O
，,O
将,O
适,O
合,O
以,O
市,O
场,O
化,O
方,O
式,O
配,O
置,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
基,O
本,O
纳,O
入,O
统,O
一,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
体,O
系,O
，,O
实,O
现,O
全,O
区,O
统,O
一,O
目,O
录,O
管,O
理,O
；,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
纵,O
向,O
全,O
面,O
贯,O
通,O
、,O
横,O
向,O
互,O
联,O
互,O
通,O
，,O
实,O
现,O
制,O
度,O
规,O
则,O
统,O
一,O
、,O
技,O
术,O
标,O
准,O
统,O
一,O
、,O
信,O
息,O
资,O
源,O
实,O
时,O
共,O
享,O
；,O
电,O
子,O
化,O
交,O
易,O
、,O
服,O
务,O
全,O
面,O
实,O
施,O
，,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
实,O
现,O
全,O
过,O
程,O
在,O
线,O
实,O
时,O
监,O
管,O
，,O
实,O
现,O
平,O
台,O
交,O
易,O
全,O
覆,O
盖,O
。,O
在,O
此,O
基,O
础,O
上,O
，,O
再,O
用,O
3,B_T
年,I_T
左,O
右,O
的,O
时,O
间,O
，,O
持,O
续,O
完,O
善,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
目,O
录,O
，,O
不,O
断,O
创,O
新,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
监,O
管,O
机,O
制,O
，,O
促,O
进,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
流,O
程,O
更,O
加,O
科,O
学,O
高,O
效,O
，,O
交,O
易,O
活,O
动,O
更,O
加,O
规,O
范,O
有,O
序,O
，,O
效,O
率,O
和,O
效,O
益,O
进,O
一,O
步,O
提,O
升,O
，,O
违,O
法,O
违,O
规,O
行,O
为,O
发,O
现,O
和,O
查,O
处,O
力,O
度,O
明,O
显,O
加,O
大,O
；,O
切,O
实,O
保,O
障,O
统,O
一,O
开,O
放,O
、,O
竞,O
争,O
有,O
序,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
市,O
场,O
健,O
康,O
运,O
行,O
，,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
满,O
意,O
度,O
明,O
显,O
提,O
升,O
，,O
营,O
商,O
环,O
境,O
持,O
续,O
优,O
化,O
，,O
有,O
力,O
助,O
推,O
经,O
济,O
社,O
会,O
发,O
展,O
。,O
二,O
、,O
基,O
本,O
原,O
则,O
（,O
一,O
）,O
坚,O
持,O
应,O
进,O
必,O
进,O
，,O
大,O
力,O
推,O
动,O
各,O
类,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
进,O
平,O
台,O
。,O
对,O
应,O
该,O
或,O
可,O
以,O
通,O
过,O
市,O
场,O
化,O
方,O
式,O
配,O
置,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
，,O
及,O
时,O
进,O
行,O
动,O
态,O
调,O
整,O
，,O
建,O
立,O
健,O
全,O
交,O
易,O
目,O
录,O
清,O
单,O
，,O
加,O
快,O
推,O
进,O
清,O
单,O
内,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
平,O
台,O
交,O
易,O
全,O
覆,O
盖,O
，,O
做,O
到,O
“,O
平,O
台,O
之,O
外,O
无,O
交,O
易,O
”,O
。,O
（,O
二,O
）,O
坚,O
持,O
统,O
一,O
规,O
范,O
，,O
大,O
力,O
深,O
化,O
平,O
台,O
整,O
合,O
和,O
互,O
联,O
共,O
享,O
。,O
在,O
政,O
府,O
主,O
导,O
下,O
，,O
全,O
面,O
整,O
合,O
规,O
范,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
，,O
不,O
断,O
完,O
善,O
分,O
类,O
统,O
一,O
的,O
交,O
易,O
制,O
度,O
规,O
则,O
、,O
技,O
术,O
标,O
准,O
和,O
数,O
据,O
规,O
范,O
，,O
确,O
保,O
按,O
照,O
国,O
家,O
相,O
关,O
规,O
范,O
要,O
求,O
实,O
现,O
平,O
台,O
互,O
联,O
互,O
通,O
和,O
信,O
息,O
实,O
时,O
共,O
享,O
。,O
（,O
三,O
）,O
坚,O
持,O
服,O
务,O
高,O
效,O
，,O
大,O
力,O
推,O
动,O
平,O
台,O
利,O
企,O
便,O
民,O
。,O
深,O
化,O
“,O
放,O
管,O
服,O
”,O
改,O
革,O
，,O
突,O
出,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
服,O
务,O
职,O
能,O
定,O
位,O
，,O
进,O
一,O
步,O
精,O
简,O
办,O
事,O
流,O
程,O
，,O
积,O
极,O
推,O
行,O
网,O
上,O
办,O
理,O
，,O
降,O
低,O
制,O
度,O
性,O
交,O
易,O
成,O
本,O
，,O
优,O
化,O
服,O
务,O
场,O
所,O
设,O
施,O
功,O
能,O
和,O
布,O
局,O
，,O
推,O
动,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
全,O
流,O
程,O
电,O
子,O
化,O
交,O
易,O
。,O
（,O
四,O
）,O
坚,O
持,O
公,O
开,O
透,O
明,O
，,O
大,O
力,O
推,O
动,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
阳,O
光,O
交,O
易,O
。,O
实,O
行,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
全,O
过,O
程,O
信,O
息,O
公,O
开,O
，,O
保,O
证,O
各,O
类,O
交,O
易,O
行,O
为,O
动,O
态,O
留,O
痕,O
、,O
可,O
追,O
溯,O
。,O
积,O
极,O
支,O
持,O
和,O
引,O
导,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
、,O
行,O
业,O
组,O
织,O
、,O
社,O
会,O
公,O
众,O
、,O
新,O
闻,O
媒,O
体,O
发,O
挥,O
外,O
部,O
监,O
督,O
作,O
用,O
，,O
大,O
力,O
推,O
进,O
线,O
上,O
线,O
下,O
多,O
部,O
门,O
协,O
同,O
监,O
管,O
，,O
优,O
化,O
信,O
用,O
监,O
管,O
和,O
智,O
慧,O
监,O
管,O
方,O
式,O
，,O
确,O
保,O
监,O
督,O
到,O
位,O
。,O
三,O
、,O
主,O
要,O
任,O
务,O
（,O
一,O
）,O
优,O
化,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
市,O
场,O
化,O
配,O
置,O
机,O
制,O
。,O
1,O
．,O
加,O
快,O
拓,O
展,O
平,O
台,O
覆,O
盖,O
范,O
围,O
。,O
将,O
全,O
区,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
覆,O
盖,O
范,O
围,O
由,O
工,O
程,O
建,O
设,O
项,O
目,O
招,O
标,O
投,O
标,O
、,O
土,O
地,O
使,O
用,O
权,O
和,O
矿,O
业,O
权,O
出,O
让,O
、,O
国,O
有,O
产,O
权,O
交,O
易,O
、,O
政,O
府,O
采,O
购,O
、,O
药,O
品,O
和,O
医,O
疗,O
器,O
械,O
采,O
购,O
、,O
海,O
域,O
使,O
用,O
权,O
出,O
让,O
等,O
，,O
逐,O
步,O
扩,O
大,O
到,O
适,O
合,O
以,O
市,O
场,O
化,O
方,O
式,O
配,O
置,O
的,O
自,O
然,O
资,O
源,O
、,O
资,O
产,O
股,O
权,O
、,O
环,O
境,O
权,O
等,O
各,O
类,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
。,O
坚,O
持,O
依,O
托,O
现,O
有,O
平,O
台,O
进,O
行,O
拓,O
展,O
，,O
满,O
足,O
各,O
类,O
交,O
易,O
服,O
务,O
需,O
要,O
，,O
已,O
整,O
合,O
纳,O
入,O
统,O
一,O
平,O
台,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
类,O
型,O
不,O
得,O
从,O
中,O
剥,O
离,O
或,O
自,O
行,O
新,O
设,O
其,O
他,O
平,O
台,O
。,O
结,O
合,O
全,O
国,O
统,O
一,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
目,O
录,O
指,O
引,O
及,O
我,O
区,O
实,O
际,O
，,O
系,O
统,O
梳,O
理,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
类,O
别,O
和,O
范,O
围,O
，,O
适,O
时,O
调,O
整,O
和,O
发,O
布,O
全,O
区,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
目,O
录,O
。,O
（,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
机,O
关,O
事,O
务,O
管,O
理,O
局,O
牵,O
头,O
，,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
各,O
行,O
业,O
行,O
政,O
主,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
参,O
与,O
）,O
2,O
．,O
创,O
新,O
资,O
源,O
配,O
置,O
方,O
式,O
。,O
对,O
于,O
林,O
权,O
、,O
水,O
权,O
等,O
全,O
民,O
所,O
有,O
的,O
自,O
然,O
资,O
源,O
，,O
市,O
政,O
设,O
施,O
租,O
赁,O
使,O
用,O
等,O
特,O
许,O
经,O
营,O
权,O
，,O
农,O
村,O
集,O
体,O
土,O
地,O
使,O
用,O
权,O
及,O
产,O
权,O
等,O
资,O
产,O
股,O
权,O
，,O
排,O
污,O
权,O
、,O
碳,O
排,O
放,O
权,O
、,O
用,O
能,O
权,O
等,O
环,O
境,O
权,O
，,O
以,O
及,O
知,O
识,O
产,O
权,O
等,O
其,O
他,O
适,O
合,O
推,O
进,O
市,O
场,O
化,O
配,O
置,O
的,O
权,O
益,O
，,O
要,O
探,O
索,O
建,O
立,O
出,O
让,O
或,O
转,O
让,O
规,O
则,O
，,O
积,O
极,O
采,O
取,O
招,O
标,O
投,O
标,O
、,O
挂,O
牌,O
拍,O
卖,O
等,O
竞,O
争,O
性,O
方,O
式,O
，,O
建,O
立,O
交,O
易,O
制,O
度,O
，,O
改,O
善,O
价,O
格,O
形,O
成,O
机,O
制,O
，,O
促,O
进,O
公,O
平,O
交,O
易,O
、,O
高,O
效,O
利,O
用,O
。,O
（,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
然,I_ORG
资,I_ORG
源,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
生,B_ORG
态,I_ORG
环,I_ORG
境,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
住,B_ORG
房,I_ORG
城,I_ORG
乡,I_ORG
建,I_ORG
设,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
水,B_ORG
利,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
农,B_ORG
业,I_ORG
农,I_ORG
村,I_ORG
厅,I_ORG
、,O
国,B_ORG
资,I_ORG
委,I_ORG
、,O
市,B_ORG
场,I_ORG
监,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
等,O
相,O
关,O
部,O
门,O
分,O
别,O
负,O
责,O
）,O
3,O
．,O
探,O
索,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
跨,O
区,O
域,O
交,O
易,O
。,O
推,O
进,O
公,O
平,O
竞,O
争,O
，,O
坚,O
决,O
杜,O
绝,O
采,O
取,O
设,O
置,O
注,O
册,O
登,O
记,O
或,O
设,O
立,O
分,O
支,O
机,O
构,O
（,O
办,O
事,O
处,O
）,O
、,O
资,O
质,O
验,O
证,O
、,O
投,O
标,O
（,O
竞,O
买,O
）,O
许,O
可,O
、,O
强,O
制,O
担,O
保,O
、,O
强,O
制,O
在,O
当,O
地,O
投,O
资,O
、,O
人,O
员,O
业,O
绩,O
考,O
核,O
等,O
无,O
法,O
律,O
法,O
规,O
依,O
据,O
的,O
限,O
制,O
性,O
措,O
施,O
实,O
行,O
地,O
方,O
保,O
护,O
或,O
行,O
业,O
垄,O
断,O
。,O
探,O
索,O
开,O
展,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
跨,O
省,O
域,O
、,O
跨,O
市,O
域,O
合,O
作,O
。,O
鼓,O
励,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
在,O
有,O
条,O
件,O
的,O
地,O
方,O
跨,O
市,O
自,O
主,O
选,O
择,O
平,O
台,O
进,O
行,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
。,O
（,O
各,O
级,O
各,O
有,O
关,O
行,O
业,O
主,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
及,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
中,O
心,O
分,O
类,O
协,O
同,O
推,O
进,O
）,O
（,O
二,O
）,O
提,O
升,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
服,O
务,O
水,O
平,O
。,O
1,O
．,O
全,O
面,O
整,O
合,O
升,O
级,O
平,O
台,O
电,O
子,O
系,O
统,O
。,O
加,O
快,O
推,O
进,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
电,O
子,O
系,O
统,O
建,O
设,O
，,O
明,O
确,O
交,O
易,O
、,O
服,O
务,O
、,O
监,O
管,O
等,O
各,O
子,O
系,O
统,O
的,O
功,O
能,O
定,O
位,O
，,O
实,O
现,O
互,O
联,O
互,O
通,O
和,O
信,O
息,O
资,O
源,O
共,O
享,O
。,O
依,O
托,O
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
数,O
字,O
政,O
务,O
一,O
体,O
化,O
平,O
台,O
，,O
同,O
步,O
统,O
筹,O
规,O
划,O
、,O
建,O
设,O
、,O
使,O
用,O
信,O
息,O
基,O
础,O
设,O
施,O
，,O
完,O
善,O
安,O
全,O
技,O
术,O
措,O
施,O
，,O
确,O
保,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
系,O
统,O
和,O
数,O
据,O
安,O
全,O
。,O
交,O
易,O
系,O
统,O
为,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
提,O
供,O
在,O
线,O
交,O
易,O
服,O
务,O
，,O
服,O
务,O
系,O
统,O
为,O
交,O
易,O
信,O
息,O
汇,O
集,O
、,O
共,O
享,O
和,O
发,O
布,O
提,O
供,O
在,O
线,O
服,O
务,O
，,O
监,O
管,O
系,O
统,O
为,O
行,O
政,O
监,O
督,O
部,O
门,O
、,O
审,O
计,O
部,O
门,O
、,O
纪,O
委,O
监,O
委,O
机,O
关,O
提,O
供,O
在,O
线,O
监,O
督,O
通,O
道,O
。,O
抓,O
紧,O
解,O
决,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
电,O
子,O
档,O
案,O
、,O
技,O
术,O
规,O
范,O
、,O
信,O
息,O
安,O
全,O
等,O
问,O
题,O
，,O
统,O
筹,O
整,O
合,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
评,O
标,O
、,O
评,O
审,O
专,O
家,O
资,O
源,O
，,O
加,O
快,O
促,O
进,O
专,O
家,O
资,O
源,O
跨,O
地,O
区,O
、,O
跨,O
行,O
业,O
共,O
享,O
，,O
实,O
现,O
远,O
程,O
异,O
地,O
评,O
标,O
、,O
评,O
审,O
常,O
态,O
化,O
，,O
减,O
少,O
人,O
为,O
干,O
扰,O
因,O
素,O
对,O
评,O
标,O
、,O
评,O
审,O
结,O
果,O
的,O
影,O
响,O
。,O
做,O
好,O
广,B_PRO
西,I_PRO
壮,I_PRO
族,I_PRO
自,I_PRO
治,I_PRO
区,I_PRO
公,I_PRO
共,I_PRO
资,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
交,I_PRO
易,I_PRO
平,I_PRO
台,I_PRO
系,O
统,O
与,O
全,O
国,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
系,O
统,O
、,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
招,O
标,O
投,O
标,O
公,O
共,O
服,O
务,O
平,O
台,O
系,O
统,O
等,O
系,O
统,O
的,O
对,O
接,O
，,O
实,O
现,O
自,O
动,O
实,O
时,O
共,O
享,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
各,O
类,O
数,O
据,O
。,O
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
数,O
据,O
除,O
在,O
法,O
定,O
媒,O
介,O
发,O
布,O
外,O
，,O
应,O
当,O
在,O
全,O
国,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
（,O
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
壮,I_LOC
族,I_LOC
自,I_LOC
治,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
）,O
同,O
步,O
发,O
布,O
。,O
促,O
进,O
数,O
字,O
证,O
书,O
（,O
C,O
A,O
）,O
在,O
全,O
区,O
范,O
围,O
内,O
跨,O
部,O
门,O
、,O
跨,O
区,O
域,O
互,O
认,O
，,O
并,O
按,O
国,O
家,O
要,O
求,O
逐,O
步,O
实,O
现,O
全,O
国,O
互,O
认,O
，,O
推,O
动,O
电,O
子,O
营,O
业,O
执,O
照,O
、,O
电,O
子,O
担,O
保,O
保,O
函,O
在,O
全,O
区,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
领,O
域,O
广,O
泛,O
应,O
用,O
。,O
在,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
下,I_T
半,I_T
年,I_T
建,O
成,O
全,O
区,O
统,O
一,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
系,O
统,O
，,O
实,O
现,O
各,O
类,O
交,O
易,O
数,O
据,O
实,O
时,O
共,O
享,O
和,O
互,O
联,O
互,O
通,O
，,O
降,O
低,O
企,O
业,O
交,O
易,O
成,O
本,O
，,O
提,O
高,O
交,O
易,O
效,O
率,O
。,O
（,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
机,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
理,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
会,O
同,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
大,I_ORG
数,I_ORG
据,I_ORG
发,I_ORG
展,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
负,O
责,O
统,O
筹,O
协,O
调,O
，,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
中,O
心,O
参,O
与,O
协,O
调,O
管,O
理,O
，,O
数,O
字,O
广,O
西,O
集,O
团,O
承,O
担,O
建,O
设,O
及,O
运,O
行,O
维,O
护,O
，,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
各,O
行,O
业,O
行,O
政,O
主,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
支,O
持,O
配,O
合,O
）,O
2,O
．,O
强,O
化,O
公,O
共,O
服,O
务,O
定,O
位,O
。,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
中,O
心,O
作,O
为,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
主,O
要,O
运,O
行,O
服,O
务,O
机,O
构,O
，,O
要,O
积,O
极,O
采,O
取,O
有,O
力,O
措,O
施,O
，,O
整,O
合,O
优,O
化,O
服,O
务,O
场,O
所,O
及,O
配,O
备,O
适,O
应,O
电,O
子,O
化,O
交,O
易,O
发,O
展,O
需,O
要,O
的,O
配,O
套,O
设,O
施,O
，,O
不,O
断,O
改,O
善,O
见,O
证,O
、,O
信,O
息,O
、,O
档,O
案,O
、,O
专,O
家,O
抽,O
取,O
等,O
服,O
务,O
，,O
开,O
展,O
交,O
易,O
大,O
数,O
据,O
分,O
析,O
，,O
为,O
宏,O
观,O
经,O
济,O
决,O
策,O
提,O
供,O
服,O
务,O
，,O
并,O
为,O
规,O
范,O
交,O
易,O
市,O
场,O
提,O
供,O
有,O
力,O
支,O
撑,O
。,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
中,O
心,O
不,O
得,O
将,O
重,O
要,O
敏,O
感,O
数,O
据,O
擅,O
自,O
公,O
开,O
及,O
用,O
于,O
商,O
业,O
用,O
途,O
。,O
除,O
法,O
律,O
法,O
规,O
明,O
确,O
规,O
定,O
外,O
，,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
中,O
心,O
不,O
得,O
代,O
行,O
行,O
政,O
监,O
管,O
职,O
能,O
，,O
不,O
得,O
限,O
制,O
交,O
易,O
主,O
体,O
自,O
主,O
权,O
；,O
在,O
确,O
保,O
平,O
台,O
稳,O
定,O
运,O
行,O
和,O
数,O
据,O
安,O
全,O
的,O
基,O
础,O
上,O
不,O
得,O
排,O
斥,O
和,O
限,O
制,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
建,O
设,O
运,O
营,O
的,O
电,O
子,O
交,O
易,O
系,O
统,O
。,O
（,O
各,O
级,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
中,O
心,O
分,O
别,O
负,O
责,O
）,O
3,O
．,O
精,O
简,O
管,O
理,O
事,O
项,O
和,O
环,O
节,O
。,O
分,O
类,O
梳,O
理,O
服,O
务,O
、,O
交,O
易,O
和,O
管,O
理,O
流,O
程,O
，,O
简,O
化,O
程,O
序,O
，,O
取,O
消,O
没,O
有,O
法,O
律,O
法,O
规,O
依,O
据,O
的,O
投,O
标,O
人,O
审,O
核,O
、,O
投,O
标,O
报,O
名,O
等,O
事,O
项,O
以,O
及,O
能,O
采,O
用,O
告,O
知,O
承,O
诺,O
制,O
和,O
事,O
中,O
事,O
后,O
监,O
管,O
解,O
决,O
的,O
前,O
置,O
审,O
批,O
或,O
审,O
核,O
环,O
节,O
。,O
实,O
行,O
多,O
业,O
务,O
合,O
并,O
申,O
请,O
，,O
以,O
“,O
一,O
表,O
申,O
请,O
”,O
方,O
式,O
一,O
次,O
性,O
收,O
集,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
基,O
本,O
信,O
息,O
材,O
料,O
，,O
促,O
进,O
后,O
续,O
重,O
复,O
使,O
用,O
、,O
及,O
时,O
更,O
新,O
。,O
推,O
行,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
服,O
务,O
“,O
一,O
网,O
通,O
办,O
”,O
，,O
分,O
类,O
规,O
范,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
服,O
务,O
事,O
项,O
，,O
公,O
开,O
办,O
理,O
程,O
序,O
，,O
不,O
断,O
提,O
高,O
服,O
务,O
事,O
项,O
网,O
上,O
办,O
理,O
比,O
例,O
。,O
（,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
机,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
理,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
牵,O
头,O
，,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
各,O
行,O
业,O
行,O
政,O
主,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
、,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
公,I_ORG
共,I_ORG
资,I_ORG
源,I_ORG
交,I_ORG
易,I_ORG
中,I_ORG
心,I_ORG
分,O
别,O
负,O
责,O
）,O
（,O
三,O
）,O
创,O
新,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
监,O
管,O
体,O
制,O
。,O
1,O
．,O
强,O
化,O
协,O
同,O
监,O
管,O
。,O
深,O
化,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
管,O
理,O
体,O
制,O
改,O
革,O
，,O
推,O
进,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
服,O
务,O
、,O
管,O
理,O
与,O
监,O
督,O
职,O
能,O
相,O
互,O
分,O
离,O
，,O
探,O
索,O
推,O
进,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
综,O
合,O
监,O
管,O
。,O
各,O
级,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
整,O
合,O
工,O
作,O
牵,O
头,O
部,O
门,O
要,O
会,O
同,O
有,O
关,O
行,O
政,O
监,O
督,O
部,O
门,O
，,O
根,O
据,O
法,O
律,O
法,O
规,O
、,O
部,O
门,O
职,O
责,O
分,O
工,O
及,O
实,O
际,O
监,O
管,O
工,O
作,O
需,O
要,O
，,O
于,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
年,I_T
6,I_T
月,I_T
3,I_T
0,I_T
日,I_T
前,I_T
形,O
成,O
监,O
管,O
权,O
力,O
和,O
责,O
任,O
清,O
单,O
并,O
向,O
社,O
会,O
公,O
开,O
。,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
各,O
行,O
业,O
行,O
政,O
主,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
要,O
分,O
别,O
建,O
立,O
健,O
全,O
投,O
诉,O
举,O
报,O
接,O
收,O
、,O
转,O
办,O
、,O
反,O
馈,O
工,O
作,O
机,O
制,O
。,O
有,O
关,O
行,O
政,O
监,O
督,O
部,O
门,O
要,O
依,O
法,O
查,O
处,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
过,O
程,O
中,O
的,O
违,O
法,O
违,O
规,O
行,O
为,O
，,O
实,O
现,O
部,O
门,O
联,O
合,O
执,O
法,O
、,O
案,O
件,O
限,O
时,O
办,O
结,O
、,O
结,O
果,O
主,O
动,O
反,O
馈,O
。,O
加,O
大,O
信,O
息,O
公,O
开,O
力,O
度,O
，,O
改,O
进,O
信,O
息,O
录,O
入,O
、,O
提,O
取,O
等,O
工,O
作,O
环,O
节,O
设,O
置,O
，,O
引,O
导,O
和,O
督,O
促,O
参,O
与,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
过,O
程,O
的,O
各,O
类,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
依,O
法,O
及,O
时,O
公,O
开,O
全,O
过,O
程,O
交,O
易,O
信,O
息,O
。,O
加,O
强,O
社,O
会,O
监,O
督,O
，,O
优,O
化,O
社,O
会,O
监,O
督,O
参,O
与,O
方,O
式,O
，,O
开,O
展,O
“,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
公,O
开,O
日,O
”,O
等,O
活,O
动,O
，,O
组,O
织,O
社,O
会,O
监,O
督,O
员,O
经,O
常,O
性,O
参,O
与,O
监,O
督,O
，,O
支,O
持,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
、,O
行,O
业,O
组,O
织,O
、,O
社,O
会,O
公,O
众,O
、,O
新,O
闻,O
媒,O
体,O
等,O
对,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
活,O
动,O
开,O
展,O
监,O
督,O
，,O
共,O
同,O
营,O
造,O
公,O
平,O
、,O
公,O
正,O
、,O
公,O
开,O
的,O
交,O
易,O
环,O
境,O
。,O
（,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
机,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
理,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
、,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
各,O
行,O
业,O
行,O
政,O
主,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
牵,O
头,O
，,O
各,O
市,O
、,O
县,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
整,O
合,O
牵,O
头,O
部,O
门,O
、,O
相,O
关,O
行,O
业,O
行,O
政,O
主,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
及,O
各,O
级,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
中,O
心,O
配,O
合,O
）,O
2,O
．,O
实,O
行,O
信,O
用,O
监,O
管,O
。,O
依,O
据,O
国,O
家,O
和,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
统,O
一,O
的,O
信,O
用,O
监,O
管,O
标,O
准,O
，,O
加,O
快,O
全,O
区,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
领,O
域,O
信,O
用,O
体,O
系,O
建,O
设,O
，,O
建,O
立,O
健,O
全,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
信,O
用,O
信,O
息,O
管,O
理,O
、,O
共,O
享,O
、,O
运,O
用,O
等,O
机,O
制,O
。,O
强,O
化,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
信,O
用,O
信,O
息,O
公,O
开,O
和,O
运,O
用,O
，,O
把,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
参,O
与,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
活,O
动,O
的,O
信,O
用,O
信,O
息,O
归,O
集,O
到,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
信,O
用,O
信,O
息,O
共,O
享,O
平,O
台,O
，,O
并,O
实,O
时,O
上,O
传,O
到,O
国,O
家,O
信,O
用,O
信,O
息,O
共,O
享,O
平,O
台,O
，,O
作,O
为,O
实,O
施,O
监,O
管,O
的,O
重,O
要,O
依,O
据,O
，,O
以,O
便,O
相,O
关,O
行,O
政,O
主,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
联,O
合,O
开,O
展,O
守,O
信,O
激,O
励,O
和,O
失,O
信,O
惩,O
戒,O
。,O
（,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
机,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
理,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
牵,O
头,O
，,O
相,O
关,O
行,O
业,O
行,O
政,O
主,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
分,O
别,O
负,O
责,O
）,O
3,O
．,O
优,O
化,O
智,O
慧,O
监,O
管,O
。,O
依,O
托,O
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
壮,I_LOC
族,I_LOC
自,I_LOC
治,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
系,O
统,O
，,O
在,O
线,O
下,O
达,O
工,O
作,O
指,O
令,O
，,O
实,O
现,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
、,O
中,O
介,O
机,O
构,O
和,O
交,O
易,O
过,O
程,O
信,O
息,O
全,O
面,O
记,O
录,O
、,O
实,O
时,O
交,O
互,O
，,O
确,O
保,O
交,O
易,O
记,O
录,O
来,O
源,O
可,O
溯,O
、,O
去,O
向,O
可,O
查,O
、,O
监,O
督,O
留,O
痕,O
、,O
责,O
任,O
可,O
究,O
。,O
强,O
化,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
活,O
动,O
实,O
时,O
在,O
线,O
监,O
测,O
分,O
析,O
，,O
科,O
学,O
运,O
用,O
先,O
进,O
的,O
信,O
息,O
技,O
术,O
手,O
段,O
，,O
监,O
控,O
并,O
自,O
动,O
预,O
警,O
围,O
标,O
串,O
标,O
、,O
弄,O
虚,O
作,O
假,O
等,O
违,O
法,O
违,O
规,O
行,O
为,O
，,O
增,O
强,O
监,O
管,O
的,O
时,O
效,O
性,O
和,O
精,O
准,O
性,O
。,O
会,O
同,O
执,O
法,O
部,O
门,O
创,O
新,O
交,O
易,O
过,O
程,O
综,O
合,O
执,O
法,O
机,O
制,O
，,O
加,O
大,O
对,O
重,O
点,O
地,O
区,O
、,O
重,O
点,O
领,O
域,O
、,O
重,O
点,O
环,O
节,O
的,O
监,O
督,O
执,O
法,O
力,O
度,O
。,O
推,O
进,O
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
壮,I_LOC
族,I_LOC
自,I_LOC
治,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
系,O
统,O
与,O
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
投,O
资,O
项,O
目,O
在,O
线,O
并,O
联,O
审,O
批,O
监,O
管,O
平,O
台,O
对,O
接,O
。,O
（,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
机,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
理,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
牵,O
头,O
，,O
相,O
关,O
行,O
业,O
行,O
政,O
主,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
、,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
公,I_ORG
共,I_ORG
资,I_ORG
源,I_ORG
交,I_ORG
易,I_ORG
中,I_ORG
心,I_ORG
、,O
数,O
字,O
广,O
西,O
集,O
团,O
分,O
别,O
负,O
责,O
）,O
四,O
、,O
组,O
织,O
保,O
障,O
（,O
一,O
）,O
加,O
强,O
领,O
导,O
，,O
形,O
成,O
工,O
作,O
合,O
力,O
。,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
机,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
理,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
要,O
会,O
同,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
有,O
关,O
部,O
门,O
，,O
结,O
合,O
全,O
区,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
应,O
进,O
必,O
进,O
等,O
实,O
际,O
需,O
要,O
，,O
完,O
善,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
整,O
合,O
工,O
作,O
厅,O
际,O
联,O
席,O
会,O
议,O
机,O
制,O
，,O
密,O
切,O
联,O
动,O
、,O
协,O
同,O
落,O
实,O
上,O
级,O
决,O
策,O
部,O
署,O
，,O
研,O
究,O
破,O
解,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
和,O
群,O
众,O
反,O
映,O
强,O
烈,O
的,O
热,O
点,O
、,O
难,O
点,O
问,O
题,O
，,O
加,O
强,O
对,O
各,O
地,O
的,O
政,O
策,O
指,O
导,O
、,O
业,O
务,O
培,O
训,O
、,O
督,O
查,O
，,O
确,O
保,O
改,O
革,O
任,O
务,O
及,O
时,O
分,O
解,O
落,O
实,O
。,O
各,O
设,O
区,O
市,O
人,O
民,O
政,O
府,O
要,O
统,O
筹,O
推,O
进,O
本,O
行,O
政,O
区,O
域,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
整,O
合,O
共,O
享,O
工,O
作,O
，,O
强,O
化,O
对,O
本,O
行,O
政,O
区,O
域,O
各,O
级,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
中,O
心,O
的,O
业,O
务,O
指,O
导,O
，,O
切,O
实,O
保,O
障,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
软,O
硬,O
件,O
设,O
备,O
更,O
新,O
和,O
运,O
行,O
维,O
护,O
的,O
经,O
费,O
，,O
加,O
强,O
信,O
息,O
技,O
术,O
方,O
面,O
培,O
训,O
和,O
能,O
力,O
建,O
设,O
，,O
加,O
大,O
人,O
员,O
、,O
设,O
施,O
等,O
配,O
套,O
保,O
障,O
力,O
度,O
，,O
层,O
层,O
落,O
实,O
各,O
项,O
工,O
作,O
。,O
（,O
二,O
）,O
完,O
善,O
制,O
度,O
，,O
理,O
顺,O
工,O
作,O
机,O
制,O
。,O
积,O
极,O
做,O
好,O
招,O
标,O
投,O
标,O
、,O
自,O
然,O
资,O
源,O
资,O
产,O
转,O
让,O
、,O
国,O
有,O
产,O
权,O
交,O
易,O
、,O
政,O
府,O
采,O
购,O
、,O
药,O
品,O
和,O
医,O
疗,O
器,O
械,O
采,O
购,O
等,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
领,O
域,O
规,O
章,O
制,O
度,O
的,O
立,O
改,O
废,O
释,O
工,O
作,O
。,O
加,O
强,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
领,O
域,O
信,O
息,O
安,O
全,O
建,O
设,O
管,O
理,O
，,O
根,O
据,O
信,O
息,O
安,O
全,O
标,O
准,O
改,O
进,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
信,O
息,O
安,O
全,O
防,O
护,O
体,O
系,O
，,O
确,O
保,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
运,O
行,O
安,O
全,O
和,O
数,O
据,O
安,O
全,O
。,O
完,O
善,O
评,O
标,O
、,O
评,O
审,O
专,O
家,O
管,O
理,O
办,O
法,O
，,O
健,O
全,O
专,O
家,O
征,O
集,O
、,O
培,O
训,O
、,O
考,O
核,O
和,O
清,O
退,O
机,O
制,O
，,O
加,O
快,O
推,O
进,O
专,O
家,O
资,O
源,O
一,O
网,O
共,O
享,O
，,O
保,O
障,O
电,O
子,O
评,O
标,O
评,O
审,O
。,O
分,O
类,O
引,O
导,O
中,O
介,O
机,O
构,O
完,O
善,O
管,O
理,O
制,O
度,O
，,O
加,O
强,O
自,O
律,O
和,O
信,O
用,O
维,O
护,O
，,O
规,O
范,O
代,O
理,O
行,O
为,O
。,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
机,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
理,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
要,O
会,O
同,O
有,O
关,O
部,O
门,O
完,O
善,O
制,O
度,O
规,O
则,O
，,O
抓,O
紧,O
对,O
不,O
符,O
合,O
整,O
合,O
共,O
享,O
要,O
求,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
制,O
度,O
规,O
则,O
及,O
相,O
关,O
工,O
作,O
方,O
案,O
进,O
行,O
清,O
理,O
，,O
并,O
及,O
时,O
公,O
告,O
清,O
理,O
过,O
程,O
和,O
结,O
果,O
；,O
抓,O
好,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
服,O
务,O
标,O
准,O
贯,O
彻,O
落,O
实,O
，,O
结,O
合,O
全,O
国,O
统,O
一,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
目,O
录,O
指,O
引,O
，,O
按,O
程,O
序,O
动,O
态,O
调,O
整,O
并,O
发,O
布,O
实,O
施,O
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
目,O
录,O
。,O
各,O
设,O
区,O
市,O
人,O
民,O
政,O
府,O
要,O
定,O
期,O
对,O
本,O
行,O
政,O
区,O
域,O
内,O
的,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
制,O
度,O
规,O
则,O
进,O
行,O
清,O
理,O
，,O
接,O
受,O
社,O
会,O
监,O
督,O
。,O
（,O
三,O
）,O
狠,O
抓,O
落,O
实,O
，,O
强,O
化,O
督,O
促,O
检,O
查,O
。,O
各,O
设,O
区,O
市,O
人,O
民,O
政,O
府,O
要,O
将,O
深,O
化,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
整,O
合,O
共,O
享,O
工,O
作,O
纳,O
入,O
政,O
府,O
目,O
标,O
考,O
核,O
管,O
理,O
，,O
加,O
强,O
对,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
领,O
域,O
公,O
共,O
服,O
务,O
、,O
行,O
政,O
监,O
管,O
和,O
市,O
场,O
规,O
范,O
等,O
工,O
作,O
情,O
况,O
的,O
监,O
督,O
检,O
查,O
，,O
建,O
立,O
市,O
场,O
主,O
体,O
和,O
第,O
三,O
方,O
评,O
议,O
机,O
制,O
，,O
并,O
向,O
社,O
会,O
公,O
开,O
相,O
关,O
情,O
况,O
；,O
加,O
强,O
对,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
监,O
管,O
部,O
门,O
、,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
中,O
心,O
及,O
其,O
工,O
作,O
人,O
员,O
的,O
监,O
督,O
，,O
健,O
全,O
廉,O
政,O
风,O
险,O
防,O
控,O
机,O
制,O
。,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
机,I_ORG
关,I_ORG
事,I_ORG
务,I_ORG
管,I_ORG
理,I_ORG
局,I_ORG
要,O
会,O
同,O
有,O
关,O
部,O
门,O
加,O
强,O
指,O
导,O
督,O
促,O
，,O
促,O
进,O
基,O
层,O
不,O
断,O
创,O
新,O
机,O
制,O
。,O
要,O
组,O
织,O
开,O
展,O
工,O
作,O
情,O
况,O
交,O
流,O
，,O
总,O
结,O
推,O
广,O
典,O
型,O
经,O
验,O
，,O
对,O
深,O
化,O
公,O
共,O
资,O
源,O
交,O
易,O
平,O
台,O
整,O
合,O
共,O
享,O
工,O
作,O
取,O
得,O
明,O
显,O
成,O
效,O
的,O
要,O
进,O
行,O
表,O
扬,O
，,O
对,O
推,O
进,O
工,O
作,O
不,O
力,O
的,O
要,O
进,O
行,O
通,O
报,O
，,O
确,O
保,O
各,O
项,O
任,O
务,O
措,O
施,O
落,O
实,O
到,O
位,O
，,O
重,O
要,O
情,O
况,O
及,O
时,O
报,O
告,O
自,B_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
人,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
。,O
现,O
批,O
复,O
如,O
下,O
：,O
一,O
、,O
同,O
意,O
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
底,O
定,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
级,O
自,O
然,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
（,O
以,O
下,O
简,O
称,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
）,O
功,O
能,O
区,O
划,O
。,O
现,O
批,O
复,O
如,O
下,O
：,O
一,O
、,O
同,O
意,O
调,O
整,O
鹿,B_LOC
寨,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
城,I_LOC
洛,I_LOC
清,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
饮,I_LOC
用,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
源,I_LOC
保,I_LOC
护,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
。,O
二,O
、,O
你,O
市,O
要,O
严,O
格,O
按,O
照,O
《,B_PRO
中,I_PRO
华,I_PRO
人,I_PRO
民,I_PRO
共,I_PRO
和,I_PRO
国,I_PRO
环,I_PRO
境,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
护,I_PRO
法,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
、,O
《,B_PRO
中,I_PRO
华,I_PRO
人,I_PRO
民,I_PRO
共,I_PRO
和,I_PRO
国,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
污,I_PRO
染,I_PRO
防,I_PRO
治,I_PRO
法,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
、,O
《,B_PRO
中,I_PRO
华,I_PRO
人,I_PRO
民,I_PRO
共,I_PRO
和,I_PRO
国,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
法,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
、,O
《,B_PRO
饮,I_PRO
用,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
护,I_PRO
区,I_PRO
污,I_PRO
染,I_PRO
防,I_PRO
治,I_PRO
管,I_PRO
理,I_PRO
规,I_PRO
定,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
、,O
《,B_PRO
广,I_PRO
西,I_PRO
壮,I_PRO
族,I_PRO
自,I_PRO
治,I_PRO
区,I_PRO
饮,I_PRO
用,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
护,I_PRO
条,I_PRO
例,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
等,O
法,O
律,O
法,O
规,O
规,O
章,O
和,O
《,B_PRO
集,I_PRO
中,I_PRO
式,I_PRO
饮,I_PRO
用,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
地,I_PRO
规,I_PRO
范,I_PRO
化,I_PRO
建,I_PRO
设,I_PRO
环,I_PRO
境,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
护,I_PRO
技,I_PRO
术,I_PRO
要,I_PRO
求,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
（,O
H,B_PRO
J,I_PRO
7,I_PRO
7,I_PRO
3,I_PRO
—,I_PRO
2,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
1,I_PRO
5,I_PRO
）,O
等,O
标,O
准,O
规,O
范,O
，,O
以,O
及,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
有,O
关,O
政,O
策,O
规,O
定,O
，,O
加,O
强,O
饮,O
用,O
水,O
水,O
源,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
的,O
规,O
范,O
化,O
建,O
设,O
和,O
管,O
理,O
，,O
确,O
保,O
饮,O
用,O
水,O
安,O
全,O
；,O
按,O
照,O
广,B_LOC
西,I_LOC
水,O
污,O
染,O
防,O
治,O
工,O
作,O
有,O
关,O
要,O
求,O
，,O
以,O
改,O
善,O
和,O
提,O
升,O
水,O
环,O
境,O
质,O
量,O
为,O
核,O
心,O
，,O
加,O
大,O
污,O
染,O
防,O
治,O
力,O
度,O
，,O
保,O
障,O
水,O
环,O
境,O
安,O
全,O
。,O
三,O
、,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
有,O
关,O
部,O
门,O
要,O
按,O
照,O
职,O
责,O
分,O
工,O
，,O
指,O
导,O
柳,B_LOC
州,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
做,O
好,O
饮,O
用,O
水,O
水,O
源,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
建,O
设,O
和,O
保,O
护,O
工,O
作,O
。,O
附,O
件,O
：,O
鹿,B_LOC
寨,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
城,I_LOC
洛,I_LOC
清,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
饮,I_LOC
用,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
源,I_LOC
保,I_LOC
护,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
调,O
整,O
方,O
案,O
广,B_PRO
西,I_PRO
壮,I_PRO
族,I_PRO
自,I_PRO
治,I_PRO
区,I_PRO
人,I_PRO
民,I_PRO
政,I_PRO
府,I_PRO
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
1,I_T
年,I_T
1,I_T
0,I_T
月,I_T
2,I_T
4,I_T
日,I_T
（,O
此,O
件,O
公,O
开,O
发,O
布,O
）,O
附,O
件,O
鹿,B_LOC
寨,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
城,I_LOC
洛,I_LOC
清,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
饮,I_LOC
用,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
源,I_LOC
保,I_LOC
护,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
调,O
整,O
方,O
案,O
为,O
加,O
强,O
饮,O
用,O
水,O
水,O
源,O
保,O
护,O
，,O
保,O
障,O
饮,O
用,O
水,O
安,O
全,O
，,O
按,O
照,O
有,O
关,O
法,O
律,O
法,O
规,O
规,O
章,O
、,O
标,O
准,O
规,O
范,O
和,O
政,O
策,O
要,O
求,O
，,O
结,O
合,O
鹿,B_LOC
寨,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
县,O
城,O
饮,O
用,O
水,O
水,O
源,O
实,O
际,O
情,O
况,O
，,O
制,O
定,O
本,O
方,O
案,O
。,O
一,O
、,O
饮,O
用,O
水,O
水,O
源,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
调,O
整,O
依,O
据,O
（,O
一,O
）,O
《,B_PRO
中,I_PRO
华,I_PRO
人,I_PRO
民,I_PRO
共,I_PRO
和,I_PRO
国,I_PRO
环,I_PRO
境,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
护,I_PRO
法,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
、,O
《,B_PRO
中,I_PRO
华,I_PRO
人,I_PRO
民,I_PRO
共,I_PRO
和,I_PRO
国,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
污,I_PRO
染,I_PRO
防,I_PRO
治,I_PRO
法,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
、,O
《,B_PRO
中,I_PRO
华,I_PRO
人,I_PRO
民,I_PRO
共,I_PRO
和,I_PRO
国,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
法,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
、,O
《,B_PRO
饮,I_PRO
用,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
护,I_PRO
区,I_PRO
污,I_PRO
染,I_PRO
防,I_PRO
治,I_PRO
管,I_PRO
理,I_PRO
规,I_PRO
定,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
、,O
《,B_PRO
广,I_PRO
西,I_PRO
壮,I_PRO
族,I_PRO
自,I_PRO
治,I_PRO
区,I_PRO
饮,I_PRO
用,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
护,I_PRO
条,I_PRO
例,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
等,O
法,O
律,O
法,O
规,O
规,O
章,O
。,O
（,O
二,O
）,O
《,B_PRO
集,I_PRO
中,I_PRO
式,I_PRO
饮,I_PRO
用,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
地,I_PRO
规,I_PRO
范,I_PRO
化,I_PRO
建,I_PRO
设,I_PRO
环,I_PRO
境,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
护,I_PRO
技,I_PRO
术,I_PRO
要,I_PRO
求,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
（,O
H,B_PRO
J,I_PRO
7,I_PRO
7,I_PRO
3,I_PRO
—,I_PRO
2,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
1,I_PRO
5,I_PRO
）,O
、,O
《,B_PRO
饮,I_PRO
用,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
护,I_PRO
区,I_PRO
划,I_PRO
分,I_PRO
技,I_PRO
术,I_PRO
规,I_PRO
范,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
（,O
H,B_PRO
J,I_PRO
3,I_PRO
3,I_PRO
8,I_PRO
—,I_PRO
2,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
1,I_PRO
8,I_PRO
）,O
、,O
《,B_PRO
地,I_PRO
表,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
环,I_PRO
境,I_PRO
质,I_PRO
量,I_PRO
标,I_PRO
准,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
（,O
G,B_PRO
B,I_PRO
3,I_PRO
8,I_PRO
3,I_PRO
8,I_PRO
—,I_PRO
2,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
2,I_PRO
）,O
、,O
《,B_PRO
生,I_PRO
活,I_PRO
饮,I_PRO
用,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
卫,I_PRO
生,I_PRO
标,I_PRO
准,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
（,O
G,B_PRO
B,I_PRO
5,I_PRO
7,I_PRO
4,I_PRO
9,I_PRO
—,I_PRO
2,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
0,I_PRO
6,I_PRO
）,O
等,O
标,O
准,O
规,O
范,O
。,O
（,O
三,O
）,O
鹿,B_LOC
寨,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
经,O
济,O
社,O
会,O
发,O
展,O
、,O
城,O
市,O
发,O
展,O
、,O
土,O
地,O
利,O
用,O
、,O
矿,O
产,O
资,O
源,O
、,O
交,O
通,O
发,O
展,O
、,O
水,O
资,O
源,O
、,O
环,O
境,O
保,O
护,O
等,O
规,O
划,O
。,O
（,O
四,O
）,O
《,B_PRO
鹿,I_PRO
寨,I_PRO
县,I_PRO
县,I_PRO
城,I_PRO
洛,I_PRO
清,I_PRO
江,I_PRO
饮,I_PRO
用,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
水,I_PRO
源,I_PRO
保,I_PRO
护,I_PRO
区,I_PRO
调,I_PRO
整,I_PRO
技,I_PRO
术,I_PRO
报,I_PRO
告,I_PRO
》,I_PRO
。,O
二,O
、,O
调,O
整,O
后,O
的,O
鹿,B_LOC
寨,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
城,I_LOC
洛,I_LOC
清,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
饮,I_LOC
用,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
源,I_LOC
保,I_LOC
护,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
划,O
定,O
范,O
围,O
本,O
次,O
对,O
鹿,B_LOC
寨,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
城,I_LOC
洛,I_LOC
清,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
饮,I_LOC
用,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
源,I_LOC
保,I_LOC
护,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
范,O
围,O
进,O
行,O
调,O
整,O
，,O
将,O
其,O
分,O
为,O
一,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
、,O
二,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
和,O
准,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
，,O
具,O
体,O
范,O
围,O
如,O
下,O
：,O
（,O
一,O
）,O
一,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
。,O
水,O
域,O
范,O
围,O
：,O
长,O
度,O
为,O
取,O
水,O
口,O
上,O
游,O
1,O
0,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
至,O
下,O
游,O
1,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
，,O
宽,O
度,O
为,O
洛,B_LOC
清,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
多,O
年,O
平,O
均,O
水,O
位,O
对,O
应,O
的,O
高,O
程,O
线,O
下,O
的,O
水,O
域,O
。,O
水,O
域,O
面,O
积,O
：,O
0,O
.,O
2,O
平,O
方,O
公,O
里,O
。,O
陆,O
域,O
范,O
围,O
：,O
一,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
水,O
域,O
沿,O
岸,O
纵,O
深,O
5,O
0,O
米,O
的,O
陆,O
域,O
范,O
围,O
。,O
陆,O
域,O
面,O
积,O
：,O
0,O
.,O
1,O
2,O
平,O
方,O
公,O
里,O
。,O
一,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
总,O
面,O
积,O
：,O
0,O
.,O
3,O
2,O
平,O
方,O
公,O
里,O
。,O
（,O
二,O
）,O
二,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
。,O
水,O
域,O
范,O
围,O
：,O
长,O
度,O
为,O
一,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
的,O
上,O
游,O
边,O
界,O
向,O
上,O
游,O
延,O
伸,O
4,O
0,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
（,O
洛,B_LOC
清,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
三,I_LOC
角,I_LOC
支,I_LOC
流,I_LOC
汇,I_LOC
入,I_LOC
口,I_LOC
，,O
距,O
龙,B_LOC
兴,I_LOC
电,I_LOC
站,I_LOC
大,I_LOC
坝,I_LOC
约,O
6,O
5,O
0,O
米,O
）,O
、,O
下,O
游,O
边,O
界,O
向,O
下,O
游,O
延,O
伸,O
2,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
，,O
宽,O
度,O
为,O
洛,B_LOC
清,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
多,O
年,O
平,O
均,O
水,O
位,O
对,O
应,O
的,O
高,O
程,O
线,O
下,O
的,O
水,O
域,O
；,O
石,B_LOC
鼓,I_LOC
河,I_LOC
支,O
流,O
长,O
度,O
为,O
自,O
汇,O
入,O
口,O
向,O
上,O
游,O
延,O
伸,O
2,O
0,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
，,O
宽,O
度,O
为,O
该,O
支,O
流,O
多,O
年,O
平,O
均,O
水,O
位,O
对,O
应,O
的,O
高,O
程,O
线,O
下,O
的,O
水,O
域,O
。,O
水,O
域,O
面,O
积,O
：,O
0,O
.,O
6,O
8,O
平,O
方,O
公,O
里,O
。,O
陆,O
域,O
范,O
围,O
：,O
一,O
级,O
、,O
二,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
水,O
域,O
沿,O
岸,O
纵,O
深,O
不,O
小,O
于,O
1,O
0,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
的,O
陆,O
域,O
（,O
一,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
陆,O
域,O
除,O
外,O
）,O
，,O
但,O
不,O
超,O
过,O
流,O
域,O
分,O
水,O
岭,O
范,O
围,O
。,O
陆,O
域,O
面,O
积,O
：,O
9,O
.,O
9,O
2,O
平,O
方,O
公,O
里,O
。,O
二,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
总,O
面,O
积,O
：,O
1,O
0,O
.,O
6,O
平,O
方,O
公,O
里,O
。,O
（,O
三,O
）,O
准,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
。,O
水,O
域,O
范,O
围,O
：,O
长,O
度,O
为,O
二,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
的,O
上,O
游,O
边,O
界,O
向,O
上,O
游,O
延,O
伸,O
6,O
4,O
8,O
0,O
米,O
至,O
桐,O
木,O
断,O
面,O
，,O
各,O
汇,O
入,O
支,O
流,O
长,O
度,O
为,O
自,O
汇,O
入,O
口,O
向,O
上,O
游,O
延,O
伸,O
2,O
0,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
，,O
宽,O
度,O
为,O
洛,B_LOC
清,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
及,O
各,O
支,O
流,O
多,O
年,O
平,O
均,O
水,O
位,O
对,O
应,O
的,O
高,O
程,O
线,O
下,O
的,O
水,O
域,O
。,O
水,O
域,O
面,O
积,O
：,O
2,O
.,O
0,O
平,O
方,O
公,O
里,O
。,O
陆,O
域,O
范,O
围,O
：,O
准,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
水,O
域,O
沿,O
岸,O
纵,O
深,O
不,O
小,O
于,O
1,O
0,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
的,O
陆,O
域,O
（,O
二,O
级,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
陆,O
域,O
除,O
外,O
）,O
，,O
但,O
不,O
超,O
过,O
流,O
域,O
分,O
水,O
岭,O
范,O
围,O
。,O
陆,O
域,O
面,O
积,O
：,O
2,O
5,O
.,O
0,O
9,O
平,O
方,O
公,O
里,O
。,O
准,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
总,O
面,O
积,O
：,O
2,O
7,O
.,O
0,O
9,O
平,O
方,O
公,O
里,O
。,O
广,B_ORG
西,I_ORG
壮,I_ORG
族,I_ORG
自,I_ORG
治,I_ORG
区,I_ORG
人,I_ORG
民,I_ORG
政,I_ORG
府,I_ORG
关,O
于,O
延,O
长,B_LOC
三,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
至,I_LOC
柳,I_LOC
州,I_LOC
等,O
3,O
条,O
高,O
速,O
公,O
路,O
临,O
时,O
收,O
费,O
期,O
限,O
的,O
批,O
复,O
（,O
桂,O
政,O
函,O
〔,O
2,O
0,O
2,O
1,O
〕,O
2,O
9,O
号,O
）,O
自,O
治,O
区,O
交,O
通,O
运,O
输,O
厅,O
、,O
发,O
展,O
改,O
革,O
委,O
、,O
财,O
政,O
厅,O
：,O
你,O
们,O
关,O
于,O
延,O
长,O
三,B_LOC
江,I_LOC
至,O
柳,B_LOC
州,I_LOC
高,I_LOC
速,I_LOC
公,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
、,O
岑,B_LOC
溪,I_LOC
至,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
汶,I_LOC
高,I_LOC
速,I_LOC
公,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
、,O
麦,B_LOC
岭,I_LOC
至,O
贺,B_LOC
州,I_LOC
高,I_LOC
速,I_LOC
公,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
主,O
线,O
临,O
时,O
收,O
费,O
期,O
限,O
的,O
请,O
示,O
收,O
悉,O
。,O
现,O
批,O
复,O
如,O
下,O
：,O
一,O
、,O
原,O
则,O
同,O
意,O
延,O
长,O
三,B_LOC
江,I_LOC
至,O
柳,B_LOC
州,I_LOC
高,I_LOC
速,I_LOC
公,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
临,O
时,O
收,O
费,O
期,O
限,O
2,B_T
年,I_T
，,O
即,O
从,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
1,I_T
年,I_T
4,I_T
月,I_T
7,I_T
日,I_T
起,I_T
至,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
3,I_T
年,I_T
4,I_T
月,I_T
6,I_T
日,I_T
止,I_T
；,O
延,O
长,O
岑,B_LOC
溪,I_LOC
至,I_LOC
水,I_LOC
汶,I_LOC
高,I_LOC
速,I_LOC
公,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
临,O
时,O
收,O
费,O
期,O
限,O
1,B_T
年,I_T
，,O
即,O
从,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
1,I_T
年,I_T
3,I_T
月,I_T
2,I_T
5,I_T
日,I_T
起,I_T
至,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
2,I_T
年,I_T
3,I_T
月,I_T
2,I_T
4,I_T
日,I_T
止,O
；,O
延,O
长,O
麦,B_LOC
岭,I_LOC
至,O
贺,B_LOC
州,I_LOC
高,I_LOC
速,I_LOC
公,I_LOC
路,I_LOC
主,O
线,O
临,O
时,O
收,O
费,O
期,O
限,O
2,B_T
年,I_T
，,O
即,O
从,O
2,B_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
1,I_T
年,I_T
3,I_T
月,I_T
1,I_T
1,I_T
日,I_T
起,I_T
至,I_T
2,I_T
0,I_T
2,I_T
3,I_T
年,I_T
3,I_T
月,I_T
1,I_T
0,I_T
日,I_T
止,O
。,O
二,O
、,O
请,O
你,O
们,O
指,O
导,O
并,O
督,O
促,O
上,O
述,O
3,O
条,O
高,O
速,O
公,O
路,O
项,O
目,O
业,O
主,O
，,O
尽,O
快,O
组,O
织,O
开,O
展,O
项,O
目,O
竣,O
工,O
验,O
收,O
工,O
作,O
。,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
的,O
面,O
积,O
、,O
范,O
围,O
和,O
功,O
能,O
分,O
区,O
不,O
得,O
随,O
意,O
调,O
整,O
和,O
改,O
变,O
。,O
1,O
公,O
顷,O
。,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
范,O
围,O
涉,O
及,O
崇,B_LOC
左,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
州,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
、,O
大,B_LOC
新,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
、,O
扶,B_LOC
绥,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
和,O
凤,B_LOC
凰,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
林,I_LOC
场,I_LOC
以,O
及,O
南,B_LOC
宁,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
西,I_LOC
乡,I_LOC
塘,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
、,O
隆,B_LOC
安,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
。,O
保,O
护,O
区,O
由,O
凤,B_LOC
凰,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
、,O
扶,B_LOC
绥,I_LOC
—,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
州,I_LOC
石,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
、,O
群,B_LOC
力,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
、,O
小,B_LOC
明,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
和,O
大,B_LOC
新,I_LOC
石,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
、,O
隆,B_LOC
安,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
、,O
西,B_LOC
乡,I_LOC
塘,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
等,O
7,O
个,O
片,O
区,O
组,O
成,O
，,O
其,O
中,O
凤,B_LOC
凰,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,O
区,O
面,O
积,O
1,O
3,O
1,O
5,O
5,O
.,O
8,O
公,O
顷,O
、,O
扶,B_LOC
绥,I_LOC
—,O
江,B_LOC
州,I_LOC
石,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
1,O
0,O
4,O
8,O
6,O
.,O
2,O
公,O
顷,O
、,O
群,B_LOC
力,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
4,O
7,O
7,O
6,O
.,O
8,O
公,O
顷,O
、,O
小,B_LOC
明,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
6,O
2,O
2,O
4,O
.,O
2,O
公,O
顷,O
、,O
大,B_LOC
新,I_LOC
石,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
6,O
7,O
8,O
7,O
.,O
8,O
公,O
顷,O
、,O
隆,B_LOC
安,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
9,O
2,O
8,O
7,O
公,O
顷,O
、,O
西,B_LOC
乡,I_LOC
塘,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
1,O
6,O
3,O
2,O
.,O
3,O
公,O
顷,O
。,O
各,O
片,O
区,O
四,O
至,O
界,O
线,O
描,O
述,O
如,O
下,O
：,O
一,O
、,O
凤,B_LOC
凰,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
凤,I_LOC
凰,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
范,O
围,O
涉,O
及,O
崇,B_LOC
左,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
州,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
、,O
扶,B_LOC
绥,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
和,O
南,B_LOC
宁,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
隆,I_LOC
安,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
。,O
北,O
起,O
九,B_LOC
坡,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
旁,O
4,O
7,O
0,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
向,O
东,O
经,O
2,O
6,O
0,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
6,O
4,O
1,O
.,O
4,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
8,O
6,O
.,O
1,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
3,O
3,O
7,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
过,O
古,O
拉,O
岺,O
向,O
东,O
北,O
，,O
过,O
5,O
4,O
7,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
6,O
2,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
8,O
5,O
.,O
2,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
西,B_LOC
子,I_LOC
岭,I_LOC
、,O
枯,B_LOC
茅,I_LOC
岭,I_LOC
、,O
三,B_LOC
顶,I_LOC
桥,I_LOC
、,O
顶,B_LOC
称,I_LOC
底,I_LOC
、,O
顶,B_LOC
岩,I_LOC
国,I_LOC
、,O
顶,B_LOC
岩,I_LOC
林,I_LOC
、,O
灵,B_LOC
前,I_LOC
、,O
坝,B_LOC
何,I_LOC
岭,I_LOC
、,O
顶,B_LOC
金,I_LOC
镭,I_LOC
、,O
吨,B_LOC
龙,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
、,O
恒,B_LOC
光,I_LOC
岭,I_LOC
至,I_LOC
九,I_LOC
坡,I_LOC
止,I_LOC
。,O
二,O
、,O
扶,B_LOC
绥,I_LOC
—,O
江,B_LOC
州,I_LOC
石,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
扶,B_LOC
绥,I_LOC
—,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
州,I_LOC
石,B_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
范,O
围,O
涉,O
及,O
崇,B_LOC
左,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
州,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
、,O
扶,B_LOC
绥,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
。,O
北,O
起,O
崇,B_LOC
左,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
州,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
更,O
羊,O
屯,O
东,O
面,O
山,O
顶,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
顶,O
向,O
东,O
过,O
3,O
7,O
4,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
3,O
6,O
1,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
至,O
山,O
脚,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
至,O
2,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
等,O
高,O
线,O
，,O
沿,O
2,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
等,O
高,O
线,O
、,O
1,O
5,O
0,O
米,O
等,O
高,O
线,O
、,O
1,O
2,O
5,O
米,O
等,O
高,O
线,O
以,O
上,O
所,O
有,O
石,O
山,O
范,O
围,O
。,O
范,O
围,O
内,O
含,O
白,B_LOC
头,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
、,O
叫,B_LOC
滑,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
等,O
。,O
三,O
、,O
群,B_LOC
力,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
群,I_LOC
力,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
涉,O
及,O
崇,B_LOC
左,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
江,I_LOC
州,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
，,O
分,O
3,O
个,O
小,O
片,O
区,O
，,O
自,O
北,O
向,O
南,O
分,O
为,O
枯,B_LOC
龙,I_LOC
小,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
、,O
集,B_LOC
林,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
小,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
和,O
岩,B_LOC
渠,I_LOC
小,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
。,O
枯,O
龙,O
小,O
片,O
区,O
东,O
起,O
和,O
伦,O
山,O
6,O
0,O
3,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
线,O
向,O
南,O
至,O
3,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
等,O
高,O
线,O
下,O
方,O
山,O
谷,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
谷,O
溪,O
流,O
向,O
西,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
过,O
6,O
4,O
3,O
.,O
8,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
6,O
5,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
6,O
5,O
8,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
至,O
枯,O
龙,O
小,O
片,O
区,O
最,O
西,O
端,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
过,O
6,O
7,O
6,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
如,O
原,O
、,O
寨,O
山,O
至,O
最,O
东,O
端,O
。,O
集,B_LOC
林,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
小,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
西,I_LOC
连,I_LOC
礼,I_LOC
智,I_LOC
林,I_LOC
场,I_LOC
，,O
东,O
连,O
凤,B_LOC
凰,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
。,O
该,O
小,O
片,O
区,O
西,O
起,O
6,O
4,O
3,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
顺,O
时,O
针,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
、,O
山,O
沟,O
等,O
明,O
显,O
地,O
貌,O
过,O
5,O
3,O
6,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
1,O
8,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
至,O
该,O
小,O
片,O
区,O
东,O
端,O
5,O
1,O
7,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
向,O
南,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
过,O
5,O
7,O
1,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
6,O
2,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
至,O
该,O
小,O
片,O
区,O
南,O
端,O
4,O
5,O
0,O
米,O
等,O
高,O
线,O
向,O
西,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
、,O
山,O
沟,O
过,O
5,O
3,O
8,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
6,O
0,O
2,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
集,O
林,O
山,O
、,O
5,O
7,O
7,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
古,B_LOC
梅,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
至,O
最,O
西,O
端,O
6,O
9,O
3,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
结,O
束,O
。,O
岩,B_LOC
渠,I_LOC
小,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
东,O
连,O
凤,B_LOC
凰,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
，,O
西,O
起,O
三,O
哈,O
秀,O
7,O
3,O
4,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
向,O
南,O
过,O
6,O
7,O
3,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
5,O
5,O
1,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
向,O
西,O
北,O
至,O
5,O
7,O
1,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
向,O
西,O
南,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
过,O
5,O
3,O
0,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
7,O
0,O
.,O
1,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
2,O
5,O
7,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
至,O
3,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
等,O
高,O
线,O
，,O
沿,O
3,O
0,O
0,O
米,O
等,O
高,O
线,O
至,O
岩,O
渠,O
山,O
沟,O
底,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
沟,O
过,O
岩,O
渠,O
山,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
过,O
6,O
1,O
1,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
至,O
最,O
北,O
端,O
4,O
3,O
1,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
向,O
东,O
，,O
过,O
坝,O
何,O
岭,O
、,O
灵,O
前,O
至,O
最,O
西,O
端,O
止,O
。,O
四,O
、,O
小,B_LOC
明,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
小,I_LOC
明,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
位,O
于,O
崇,B_LOC
左,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
大,I_LOC
新,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
，,O
北,O
起,O
牛,B_LOC
角,I_LOC
岭,I_LOC
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
向,O
东,O
过,O
隆,B_LOC
安,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
、,O
大,B_LOC
新,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
分,O
界,O
线,O
，,O
过,O
蒙,O
羊,O
岭,O
、,O
4,O
3,O
2,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
4,O
9,O
6,O
.,O
0,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
、,O
7,O
7,O
4,O
.,O
5,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
（,O
渌,O
头,O
）,O
至,O
最,O
西,O
端,O
6,O
1,O
3,O
.,O
1,O
高,O
程,O
点,O
，,O
沿,O
山,O
脊,O
向,O
北,O
至,O
牛,B_LOC
角,I_LOC
岭,I_LOC
止,O
。,O
五,O
、,O
大,B_LOC
新,I_LOC
石,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
大,I_LOC
新,I_LOC
石,I_LOC
山,I_LOC
片,I_LOC
区,I_LOC
范,O
围,O
涉,O
及,O
崇,B_LOC
左,I_LOC
市,I_LOC
大,I_LOC
新,I_LOC
县,I_LOC
和,O
